<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LRSSTreeNodes xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <nodes>
    <LRSRSSTreeNode>
      <feed>
        <URL>http://hoser.lander.ca/SyndicationService.asmx/GetRss</URL>
        <Title>CLR Hoser</Title>
        <Description>newtelligence powered</Description>
        <PubDate>0001-01-01T00:00:00</PubDate>
        <Items>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Correctness (AKA: Why I work on the CLR Team)</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   I've been working on the CLR team now for slightly over 2 years (FYI: been at MSFT
   for 5.5). I've learned a great deal in that time about managed code (and native code
   too), new programming concepts, managing large teams (there are about 150 us now)
   and some other odds and sundries. I've also had access to early hardware from our
   friends at AMD and Intel.&amp;nbsp;None of that surprises me now, nor would it have suprised
   me back in late 2003 (when I started). One concept that&amp;nbsp;I have picked up that
   I didn't expect was around correctness. Maybe I just missed class the day they taught
   "correctness", but it was new to me, at least to the degree it is taken seriously
   on this team.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   I took a look @ Wikipedia to see what it thought about &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Correctness"&gt;correctness&lt;/a&gt;.
   The definition there flirts with what I think of correctness, but it isn't quite it.
   The closest bit on Wikipedia is this bit:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   "In theoretical &lt;a title="Computer science" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Computer_science"&gt;computer
   science&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;b&gt;correctness&lt;/b&gt; of an &lt;a title=Algorithm href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Algorithm"&gt;algorithm&lt;/a&gt; is
   asserted when it is said that the algorithm is correct with respect to a &lt;a title="Program specification" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Program_specification"&gt;specification&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;i&gt;Functional&lt;/i&gt; correctness
   refers to the input-output behaviour of the algorithm (i.e., for each input it produces
   the correct output)."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   If I can construe those two sentences into something slightly more precise, w/rt what
   I'm thinking ...&amp;nbsp;An algorithm can be considered correct if it produces a result
   that is predictable (including predictably random)&amp;nbsp;and satisfies the requirements
   of all of its users (including potential users) under all required scenarios (including
   potential scenarios).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Another way of thinking of this is not going half-way with an implementation for some
   method. You need to solve the entire problem from all angles. You need to consider
   the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkish_dotted_and_dotless_I"&gt;turkish i&lt;/a&gt; and
   the multiple sort orders of the &lt;a href="http://www.open-std.org/jtc1/sc22/wg20/docs/n1052-Thai-ordering.pdf"&gt;thai
   character set&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(sorry:pdf link). You also have to consider &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=143582"&gt;proper
   locking semantics&lt;/a&gt;, avoiding race conditions and dead locks when called/exercised
   from multiple threads. One can all consider &lt;a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/en-us/cpref/html/frlrfSystemCollectionsArrayListClassTopic.asp"&gt;"not
   guaranteed to be thread safe"&lt;/a&gt; as another form of correctness, since the contract
   is specified up front. One could argue that stance though. You also have to ensure
   that you clearly specify the expected behaviour of operations, particularly when &lt;a href="http://msdn2.microsoft.com/library/system.int64.aspx"&gt;casting
   between data types&lt;/a&gt;. You also have to determine what should be done when you run
   out of stack, memory or other resources. What happens when the machine loses power
   in the middle of an operation. Are you in a &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=142120"&gt;consistent
   state&lt;/a&gt; when the machine comes back to life?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   So, back to the CLR team ... I find that the concept of correctness comes up a lot
   in our design sessions and general conversations. The world, in a very real way, is
   building massive amounts of code across an infinite number of possibilies and scenarios
   on top of the runtime. It is impossible for each (or any) of us on the CLR team to
   understand all of those scenarios, let alone take them all into consideration at each
   step during our development. Instead, we try to learn about as many weird and wacky
   ones as possible to help us, but correctness is really the thing that guides us each
   day. It may well turn out that our platform is not feature-rich enough in some niche
   areas. That's fine, and will always be the case to some degree. Developers still need
   to write code ;) What isn't acceptable is that our platform operates incorrectly (lack
   of correctness) in some corner case (or worse yet, general case) scenario. Provided
   that we&amp;nbsp;think hard and build correctness&amp;nbsp;into&amp;nbsp;every layer&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;our
   platform and line of code, we can&amp;nbsp;be certain that the&amp;nbsp;runtime will perform
   properly and correctly in those infinite number&amp;nbsp;of possibilities and scenarios.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   That's one of the reasons why I love working on this team ... not as much because
   I want to ensure that the runtime is correct in all cases, but because I find it incredibly
   interesting learning what the correct behaviour is in all those cases. Sometimes it
   is obvious, but other times it requires a lot of thought to understand why something
   is correct if done that way. And even more interesting yet is when you're the guy
   (or gal) who needs to determine what the correct behaviour is, and defend it to your
   peers. That sort of analysis and hard thinking definitely requires those extra brain
   cells and cycles that are not neccessarily used every day. And then you sleep really
   well the next night ;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=69d7fea0-f734-48d7-b9d9-25a8a3bbca5e" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/CorrectnessAKAWhyIWorkOnTheCLRTeam.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-10T19:03:46-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>GACUtil v2.0 -- Where to Get it</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   I &lt;a href="http://hoser.lander.ca/GacutilV20.aspx"&gt;posted&lt;/a&gt; almost a month ago about
   all the searches that I've been&amp;nbsp;noticing on&amp;nbsp;my blog&amp;nbsp;about gacutil.exe.
   I believe I've determined the question that at least some of the folks are wanting
   to ask. Folks don't know where to get it.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   gacutil.exe and other tools such as ildasm.exe are part of the &lt;a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/netframework/downloads/updates/default.aspx"&gt;.NET
   Framework&amp;nbsp;SDK&lt;/a&gt;. The .Net Framework admin tool, which used to be&amp;nbsp;part
   of the redist,&amp;nbsp;is now part of the SDK.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   There may be some confusion around gacutil in particular. It has never shipped with
   the redist, but apparently a servicing package of the redist in the Everett (v1.1)
   timeframe used it as part of its servicing logic (oops) and didn't properly clean
   up after itself (double oops). As a result, there may be developers out there that
   have gotten used to gacutil being in the framework directory. If that's the case,
   we're sorry for giving the wrong impression. gacutil is intended to be a developer-only
   tool, used as part of development.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Instead of using gacutil at deployment time (as our not-so-smart servicing package
   did), you should use MSI or code against the &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/junfeng/articles/229648.aspx"&gt;fusion
   APIs&lt;/a&gt; yourself (with the former being the preferred method).&amp;nbsp;For more info,
   you might take a look through &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/junfeng/default.aspx"&gt;Junfeng's
   blog&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Happy GACing.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=86a83ac9-6bbe-41de-92c9-26bbf228ca60" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/GACUtilV20WhereToGetIt.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-06T01:43:16-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Anonymous Delegates vs. Anonymous Methods</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   I'm still on this anonymous delegates kick. Maybe I'm on the wrong team and should
   consider a move to the C# team?? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   I've seen references to the feature of anonymous delegates as both "anonymous delegates"
   and "anonymous methods". From a philosophical standpoint, both seem like bad names.
   It had been bothering me for a while, so I decided to ask my fellow CLR buddy,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.bluebytesoftware.com/blog/"&gt;Joe&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;the
   question. Joe is a good person to go to since he's a lot smarter than me. Joe handles
   concurrency and threading for our team. Joe was doing such a good job at concurrency
   that they decided that he could handle another job ;)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Anyway, Joe agreed that both names are misleading. Here's what we came up with for
   what the features would be if you interpreted the names literally:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   - anonymous delegates: the ability to define a delegate (the actual &lt;a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/default.asp?url=/library/en-us/csspec/html/vclrfcsharpspec_15_1.asp"&gt;declaration&lt;/a&gt;)
   in a more dynamic manner, in which you do not need to statically define the signature/contract
   of the delegate up-front. &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/joelpob/"&gt;Joel&lt;/a&gt; and I
   did a quick co-routines implementation on top of the framework last summer. My first
   thought was to use delegates. This failed pretty quickly given that you need to delegate
   signature to be something better than "public delegate Object[] CoRoutineDelegate(Object[])".
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   - anonymous methods: the ability to define and generate a method in a more dynamic
   manner, in which you do not need to statically define the signature/contact of the
   method up-front or care which class it sites on. All you really want here is some
   sort of handle/reference to that method that you can pass around and call through
   as needed.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   The second definition here feels a lot more like what I've been calling anonymous
   delegates. In fact, that's more or less how this feature that we've been discussing
   actually works.&amp;nbsp;I guess "anonymous methods" is really a better term.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Just for kicks, I decided to make a category on &lt;a href="http://hoser.lander.ca/CategoryView,category,AnonymousMethods.aspx"&gt;anonymous
   methods&lt;/a&gt; so that folks can link back to all the posts, since there are quite a
   few now. I'm hoping that this post was the last one on the subject, unless I get some
   interesting&amp;nbsp;feedback from the C#&amp;nbsp;team.&amp;nbsp;With that, it's now time to
   get back to my &lt;a href="http://hoser.lander.ca/CategoryView,category,Wonders%20of%20Whidbey%20Factoring%20Features.aspx"&gt;factoring
   features in Whidbey series&lt;/a&gt;, which is in dire need of some attention.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=8514e6f1-ae11-452b-ad15-c52a445187de" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/AnonymousDelegatesVsAnonymousMethods.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-05T14:07:09-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Anonymous Delegates in C# v2.0 -- Are They Lexical Closures?</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;I recently posted twice (&lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://hoser.lander.ca/PermaLink,guid,20c75894-5947-4a62-a9c6-01b14516ecf8.aspx"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;one&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt; and &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://hoser.lander.ca/PermaLink,guid,3139853d-eff9-41ff-989f-4f6697946453.aspx"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;two&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;)
   on anonymous delegates. I guess they really caught my attention for some reason, even
   though I've known about them for a long time. The remaining question to close out
   this debate is whether anonymous delegates are the .Net Framework answer to closures.
   Another related topic is continuations. I'm certain that these are not that.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;First, what is a closure? &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;Here is how wikipedia defines &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Closure_%28computer_science%29"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;closures&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;:&amp;nbsp;
   "Unlike garden-variety functions which retain no memory of what happened in previous
   calls, &lt;b&gt;closures are capable of storing information across function calls&lt;/b&gt;."&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #003300; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;Here
   is another &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gnu.org/software/guile/docs/guile-ref/About-Closure.html"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;explanation&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;&amp;nbsp;from &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gnu.org/software/guile/"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;guile&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;,
   which is an open source&amp;nbsp;scheme interpreter that I've never heard of before: "The
   concept of &lt;dfn&gt;&lt;span style="FONT-FAMILY: Verdana"&gt;closure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/dfn&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt; is
   the idea that a lambda expression "captures" the variable bindings that are in lexical
   scope at the point where the lambda expression occurs. The procedure created by the
   lambda expression can refer to and mutate the captured bindings, and the values of
   those bindings persist between procedure calls. "&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
   &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #003300; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;My
   definition is (as of 5 mins ago): a &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="FONT-FAMILY: Verdana"&gt;closure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is
   the outcome of capturing both the in-scope variables used by a&amp;nbsp;block of code&amp;nbsp;and
   the block of code itself to the end of preserving their relationship beyond the normal
   lifetime of those in-scope local variables. As a result, the local variables can be
   shared across all calls to the block of code (i.e. method).&amp;nbsp; &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;So,&amp;nbsp;do anonymous delegates&amp;nbsp;in C# v2.0 conform to the&amp;nbsp;definition
   of&amp;nbsp;lexical closures? That seems to be a matter of great debate. It is amazing
   when you start to look at a topic and then you realize that there has been a whole
   crowd to the party before you. Anonymous delegates in C# appear to be just such a
   topic. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/default.aspx"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;Brad&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt; appears
   to have been interested in the topic &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2004/08/03/207164.aspx"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;about
   a year ago&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;. Brad takes the stance (at least at that
   time) that anonymous delegates &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2004/08/03/207164.aspx#209296"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;are
   not closures&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/abhinaba"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;abhinaba&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt; also
   takes the same &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/abhinaba/archive/2005/08/08/448939.aspx"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;stance&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://c2.com/cgi/wiki?DanMuller"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;Dan
   Muller&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt; takes the opposite opinion, believing that C# &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://c2.com/cgi/wiki?LexicalClosure"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;has
   implemented closures&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;I've come to the conclusion that anonymous delegates are closures.
   If you look at my somewhat-in-depth explanation of anonymous delegates in my &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://hoser.lander.ca/PermaLink,guid,3139853d-eff9-41ff-989f-4f6697946453.aspx"&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;last&amp;nbsp;post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;,
   you'll see that the way they work seems to conform to the three definitions above.
   In summary, the C# compiler generates a class on your behalf which contains both an
   instance method (which is your anonymous delegate) and fields that map directly to
   the in-scope variables that you access in the containing method. All access to these
   variables are wired up to these generated fields on the class. That generated class
   is in itself the closure. Being heap-allocated, it naturally can have a different
   lifetime than what the containing method has on the stack, given that stack-frames
   have a tendency to go way.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;I have a mail out to the C# team asking them their opinion on
   this interesting subject. I'm curious to see how they'll respond.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=1ae8f9b3-766b-49cc-a3dd-f7aa4cf3bcfa" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/AnonymousDelegatesInCV20AreTheyLexicalClosures.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-03T00:40:06-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Another Anonymous Delegate Example </Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   Here is a better example of using an anonymous delegate that proves, in my mind,&amp;nbsp;that
   they are lexical closures. I sure hope &lt;a href="http://hoser.lander.ca/PermaLink,guid,1ae8f9b3-766b-49cc-a3dd-f7aa4cf3bcfa.aspx"&gt;my
   definition &lt;/a&gt;of closures is correct ;)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Here's the code. Please do guess what it does or better yet, compile and run it. The
   important aspect is to guess which values of "s" do or do not match.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;using&lt;/span&gt; System;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;using&lt;/span&gt; System.Threading;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;namespace&lt;/span&gt; AnonDelegateTest2&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; Program&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;delegate&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;void&lt;/span&gt; FunkyDelegate();&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;static&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;void&lt;/span&gt; Main(&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;string&lt;/span&gt;[]
args)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
FunkyDelegate fd &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; GetDelegate();&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;for&lt;/span&gt; (Int32
i &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; 0;
i &amp;lt; 10; i++)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
fd();&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;static&lt;/span&gt; FunkyDelegate
GetDelegate()&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
String s &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; DateTime.Now.Ticks.ToString();&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
FunkyDelegate fd &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;delegate&lt;/span&gt;()&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Console.WriteLine(&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: #666666; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: #e4e4e4"&gt;"Entering
fd"&lt;/span&gt;);&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Console.WriteLine(s);&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
s &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; DateTime.Now.Ticks.ToString();&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Thread.Sleep(100);&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Console.WriteLine(s);&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Console.WriteLine(&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: #666666; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: #e4e4e4"&gt;"Leaving
fd"&lt;/span&gt;);&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Console.WriteLine();&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
};&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; fd;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=d5cf6962-ad80-4a69-893a-5c1a6f5f3c44" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/AnotherAnonymousDelegateExample.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-02T21:06:27-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Anonymous Delegates -- Explained</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   I &lt;a href="http://hoser.lander.ca/PermaLink,guid,20c75894-5947-4a62-a9c6-01b14516ecf8.aspx"&gt;posted
   an interesting bit&lt;/a&gt; of C# a couple weeks ago relating to anonymous delegates. I
   asked in that post what the result of the following code is. Here is the code and
   then the result
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;strong&gt;Code:&lt;br&gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;using&lt;/span&gt; System;&lt;br&gt;
   &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;using&lt;/span&gt; System.Threading;&lt;br&gt;
   &lt;br&gt;
   &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;namespace&lt;/span&gt; AnonMethods&lt;br&gt;
   {&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; Program&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; {&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;static&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;void&lt;/span&gt; Main(&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;string&lt;/span&gt;[]
   args)&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; {&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;for&lt;/span&gt; (Int32
   i &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; 0;
   i &amp;lt; 20; i++)&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; {&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
   Thread t &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;new&lt;/span&gt; Thread(&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;delegate&lt;/span&gt;()
   { Thread.Sleep(10); Console.WriteLine(i); });&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
   t.Start();&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; }&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Thread.Sleep(5000);&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; }&lt;br&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; }&lt;br&gt;
   }&lt;br&gt;
   &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;strong&gt;Result:&lt;br&gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;6&lt;br&gt;
   6&lt;br&gt;
   6&lt;br&gt;
   6&lt;br&gt;
   6&lt;br&gt;
   9&lt;br&gt;
   12&lt;br&gt;
   12&lt;br&gt;
   12&lt;br&gt;
   13&lt;br&gt;
   13&lt;br&gt;
   13&lt;br&gt;
   15&lt;br&gt;
   15&lt;br&gt;
   19&lt;br&gt;
   20&lt;br&gt;
   20&lt;br&gt;
   20&lt;br&gt;
   20&lt;br&gt;
   20
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why?&lt;br&gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;That's the strangest result from a for loop that I've ever seen. First, I'd
   suggest that you compile the code for yourself (remember, &lt;a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/vstudio/express/visualCsharp/default.aspx"&gt;C#
   Express&lt;/a&gt; is free) and then take and then decompile it in either ildasm or &lt;a href="http://www.aisto.com/roeder/dotnet/"&gt;Reflector&lt;/a&gt;.
   I find the C# in Reflector a whole lot easier to read than the IL, so I'd recommend
   that you start with it. I imagine that you'll get a real kick out of what you see.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;First, I'd like to caveat my explanation by saying that this is
   a CLR guy's explanation of what the C# compiler is doing. I haven't talked to the
   C# team, but&amp;nbsp;just took a look at the code emitted by the compiler, which both
   you and I are free to&amp;nbsp;ponder. All that being said,&amp;nbsp;here's the basic idea
   of what I think is going&amp;nbsp; on without going into great detail of the mechanics
   of anonymous delegates. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;Once the C# source code is&amp;nbsp;compiled, the anonymous delegate
   goes away and is replaced by the mechanism that I'm about to describe. Put another
   way, anonymous delegates are a C# source-code-only feature. For every anonymous delegate,
   there is a strangely, but probably predictably, named&amp;nbsp;nested class added to the
   class that indirectly contained (within one of the methods within the class)&amp;nbsp;the
   anonymous delegate.&amp;nbsp;The class, as you might expect, exposes some surface area
   that is accessed from the parent class. The class is actually private, which means
   it cannot be accessed from anywhere but the parent class.&amp;nbsp;There is a default
   constructor, which does nothing. There is a method that is the anonymous delegate
   transformed into a regular named method. Remember, anonymous delegates are a C#, not
   a CLR feature, so the CLR does need a named method to call. Lastly, there are a set
   of fields exposed on this compiler-generated class -- and this is the part that gets
   interesting -- that are the&amp;nbsp;local&amp;nbsp;variables&amp;nbsp;that are accessed from
   both the containing method and the anonymous delegate. Variables that are defined
   in the containing method but not accessed from within the anonymous delegate or that
   are defined and used within the anonymous delegate do not get this special treatment.
   As you might guess, the C# compiler wires up the method that takes the delegate and
   the generated named method. In addition, all accesses to the shared local variables
   are wired up through the public fields on the generated class instead of through the
   actual locals. Very interesting.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;OK, so that's the basic explananation of how anonymous delegates
   work. There are some other subtleties that I noticed, but they are not important for
   this explanation. I'm going to get further insight on those from the C# team and will
   post on those when I learn more about them.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;So, then, how does all that lead to the strange and unexpected
   results from the for loop. Well, since the "i" variable is accessed by both the containing
   method and the anonymous delegate, the C# compiler rewires all accesses to "i" to
   the "i" field on the generated class. And since each call to the anonymous delegate
   in our example does its work on a separate thread, then "i" is updated by the for
   loop on a different schedule than it is written by Console.WriteLine in the anonymous
   delegate. That's&amp;nbsp;why the value printed&amp;nbsp;out by each call to the anonymous
   delegate is essentially a race condition between the for loop continually iterating
   and threads being &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;created and getting time on the processor(s).&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;Another aspect of this is that&amp;nbsp;shared locals&amp;nbsp;with anonymous
   delegates essentially turn value types into reference types.&amp;nbsp;That's a really
   strange behaviour and realization.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;Like I said in the earlier post, the trick is determining a scenario
   where this behaviour is useful. I haven't found that yet, although I'm sure it will
   be very interesting once I find it.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=3139853d-eff9-41ff-989f-4f6697946453" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/AnonymousDelegatesExplained.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-30T10:51:11-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>The Count of Monte Bristowe, St. Jerome and Zed</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   I'm hanging out at Microsoft Calgary at this point. I'm still recovering from the
   Calgary launch yesterday, which involved standing for several hours answering lots
   and lots of questions. Actually, the standing wasn't that bad. My favourite part though
   was the Q&amp;amp;A at the end of the day. I'd say that Calgary was probably our best
   stop on the tour for Q&amp;amp;A, with the caveat that I did not attend the Toronto Q&amp;amp;A
   (even though I was in the building). The Calgary folks provided us with a constant
   stream of high-quality questions, including a string of them on &lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/windows/onecare"&gt;Windows
   OneCare&lt;/a&gt;, which we really were not able to&amp;nbsp;answer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   The only bad thing is that my notebook hard-drive failed yesterday at the launch.
   I knew something was bad when the BSOD popped up on my XP machine. Gotta say that
   that never happens on XP, contrary to the belief of the Slashdot crowd. They'll likely
   need to put on their &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Slashdot_subculture#Tinfoil_Hat"&gt;tin-foil
   hats&lt;/a&gt; to read/hear that. My buddy Marc -- whom I'm staying with in Calgary -- graciously
   leant me his PIII Thinkpad for the day. It is slower than my regular machines (particularly
   compared to my X64 machines with 4 times more RAM back at the office), but it sure
   works better than my cooked laptop.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Well, I'm at the end of my tour-of-duty on the VS 2005 Launch: Canadian Edition. I
   really enjoyed myself hanging out with the MS Canada folks, in Toronto, Ottawa, Vancouver
   and Calgary. In particular, there was a set of us that spent a lot of time in the
   experts area (while not presenting), answering and routing customer questions among
   each other. It was tough to beat the expertise held by the &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/jbristowe/archive/2005/11/25/496913.aspx"&gt;Count&lt;/a&gt; and
   the &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/jcarron"&gt;Saint&lt;/a&gt;. They could pretty much answer
   anything from Com+ to Windows Forms, with a whole lot in between. I noticed a&amp;nbsp;bunch
   of interesting diagrams that the both of them&amp;nbsp;constructed on the paper boards
   (cannot think of a better term). Can you say &lt;a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/webservices/indigo/default.aspx"&gt;WCF&lt;/a&gt;?&amp;nbsp;And
   Zed was our man when it came to VSTS, particularly licensing and the apparent mystery
   of VS SKUs. We were constantly calling him over, as there were *a lot* of questions
   relating to VSTS.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   I also enjoyed "experting" with the bunch of the folks that joined us in one or more
   of the other cities. We had a lot of fun together, on and off the field.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   That's all not to mention all of the developer/IT Pro folks that we met in each city.
   I had a lot of interesting conversations with our customers all over Canada. You are
   the ones that make our platform so successful. You are also the reason why I put so
   much effort into the CLR, back in Redmond. It sounds like a marketing-line, but it
   is true. We spend a lot of time in conference rooms, hallways and each other's offices
   (not to mention mail) talking about how customers are going to use our product.&amp;nbsp;Invariably,
   we&amp;nbsp;broaden what seems like a simple scenario into something a fair bit more significant,
   but that will delight and empower a much larger (hopefully all of them) set of customers.
   That's what it's all about.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Thanks again to everyone I met on the launch tour. I hope that you got as much out
   of the experience as I did.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   I'm now back to Team CLR, back in rainy Redmond.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=e9ffdd93-76ee-44f0-9dcc-2382d48e7c2c" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/TheCountOfMonteBristoweStJeromeAndZed.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-25T13:50:12-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>The Wonders of Whidbey Factoring Features – Part III: Friend Assemblies</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;We’re now at least half way into
   this set of posts on factoring features in Visual Studio 2005. The more I’ve thought
   about getting this set of posts fully written up, the more I’ve found these features
   interesting. My team produced them, so that helps, but I believe that a lot of developers
   will end up needing these features as a part of their versioning plan.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal"&gt;&lt;font size=3&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;&lt;font face="Times New Roman"&gt;AKA
   InternalsVisibleTo&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
   &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;Friend assemblies are a nickname
   for the InternalsVisibleTo attribute in the System.Runtime.CompilerServices namespace.
   Not much of a stretch from the name, the use of the attribute allows you to specify
   which assemblies (your friends) should have access to your internal types and members.
   Just to remind you, “internal” != “private” – “internal” == “internal”.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;As you might guess, this attribute
   must be set at the assembly-level. You might hope, however, that you could set this
   attribute at a more fine-grained level. I can explain that more later.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal"&gt;&lt;font size=3&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;&lt;font face="Times New Roman"&gt;Syntax&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
   &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;The attribute is set in the following
   way:&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;[assembly:InternalsVisibleTo(“MyOtherAssembly,
   PublicKey=4asdsadasdsd”)&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;Couple things … The constructor
   of the attribute -- remember attributes are just types -- takes a textual assembly
   identity. Next, you must specify at least an assembly name and optionally a public
   key token. You can specify a culture as long as it is neutral. You cannot specify
   a version. Some of this may be a surprise to you. I’ll explain that below.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal"&gt;&lt;font size=3&gt;&lt;font color=#000000&gt;&lt;font face="Times New Roman"&gt;Design
   Decision Points&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
   &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;In retrospect, I’m not sure that
   making the public key token optional was the absolute best idea, but it was probably
   was necessary for a lot of interesting scenarios. First, friend assemblies is not
   a security feature, in the sense that visibility is not a security feature. Friend
   assemblies is just about changing the usual bounds of visibility to something that
   is more convenient for developers in a lot of cases.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;That all being said, friend assemblies
   are really best kept to strong-named assemblies. Weak- or simple-named are very easily
   spoof-able (by definition). As a result, someone can simply use a particular name
   for their assembly and then get access to the internal fields in a simply-named assembly
   from which you’ve granted friendship. Even if you only ship your code internally within
   your business, this still isn’t a great plan. Think about it for a while and you’ll
   probably begin to better understand why.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;It probably mostly goes without
   saying, but strong-named assemblies can only have strong-named friends. Strong-named
   assemblies can only depend on strong-named assemblies, so this point is moot anyway.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;I do feel strongly that disallowing
   the version number was the right thing to do. The reason for that is that CLR binding
   doesn’t always produce the version of an assembly that you expect. There are a lot
   of mechanisms that can be at play, such as publisher policy, binding-redirects and
   other binding/versioning changes that we have planned for the CLR v3. As a result,
   you cannot assume that an assembly that depends on you is always going to be the same.
   Remember, with friends, it isn’t that you are assuming that a dependency of yours
   is going to be a particular version, but an assembly that is dependent on you. We
   would have potentially made a different decision if friends was the opposite way around,
   being a statement about your dependencies, but it isn’t.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;o:p&gt;
      &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/o:p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font face="Times New Roman" color=#000000 size=3&gt;The ability to specify culture provided
   that it is neutral is mostly a red-herring. There is no harm to specifying it, which
   is why we allowed it, but it is best to think in general that culture isn’t allowed.
   The main reason here is that you should not have code in culture-specific assemblies.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=e3c1498a-2a48-4ab4-ba16-cb4de3fee73b" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/TheWondersOfWhidbeyFactoringFeaturesPartIIIFriendAssemblies.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-21T13:46:14-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Going to VS Launch in Vancouver and Calgary</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   I'll be attending the Visual Studio 2005 launches in both Vancouver and Calgary next
   week.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   I'm definitely looking forward to both. I'm up to Vancouver all the time, being only
   about&amp;nbsp;2 hours to the Canadian border from Redmond, plus parts of my family lives
   in Cloverdale. I'm very curious what the Vancouver .Net crowd is like. I have to admit
   that the Toronto crowd blew me away, with a turnout of &amp;gt;3000 developers and IT
   professionals. I guess I should admit that a bunch of those might just have happened
   to be there for SQL Server 2005 or Biztalk 2006. That being said, it did seem like
   the VS 2005/.NET Framework&amp;nbsp;"experts" in the "Ask the Experts" area were particularly
   busy.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   I haven't been to Calgary since ~2001. My best friend lives there, so we'll likely
   hit the slopes (Rockie mountains) if the weather co-operates.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Please introduce yourself at the launches if you are able to make it. I'll be in the
   experts area most of the time. Also, please mail me if you'd like to setup some time
   to meet, either at the launch or elsewhere, to discuss development issues. I had good
   luck meeting with banks in Toronto and would like to have similar meetings in the
   West. I guess I should ring up the oil patch while in Calgary and see how they're
   using .Net.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   Us "experts" typically have dinner together directly after the launch. Please mail
   me if you'd like to join us. This is a good chance to spend 90mins with the likes
   of &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/jbristowe/"&gt;John&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/jcarron/"&gt;Jerome&lt;/a&gt;.
   John refers to himself as a &lt;a href="http://plumbersatwork.com/"&gt;plumber&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=bacfd93b-a51d-439b-b567-ea13bb5603db" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/GoingToVSLaunchInVancouverAndCalgary.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-17T00:50:54-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Gacutil v2.0</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   Most blog engines support some notion of referrers, listing where your traffic came
   from. This includes search engines and the search terms that were used. There are
   definitely some strong trends, largely related to what MSN Search and Google think
   my blog is about. If I wrote about new moons being discovered in pluto's orbit, then
   I'd start to get more traffic on that.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   That all being said, I'm getting a fair number of searches coming through on gacutil
   v2.0. That isn't strange on its own. I'm glad that folks are using it. My&amp;nbsp;question
   is what in particular folks are searching for. If you are one of those folks that
   are searching for something on gacutil v2.0 in VS 2005, please enter a comment below
   describing the data that you are looking for. Feel free to mail me @ &lt;a href="mailto:rlander@microsoft.com"&gt;rlander@microsoft.com&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   As an aside, I get pretty much no spam at the address above, which is why I don't
   mind listing it.&amp;nbsp;The combination of Exchange 12 and&amp;nbsp;Outlook 2003 must be
   pretty amazing at eating spam. I'm on Exchange 12 dogfood, as is the rest of the CLR
   team.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=15213d59-4a8a-498d-b57e-1828759d840c" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/GacutilV20.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-15T12:30:02-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Anonymous Delegates</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   What does the following C# code do? Guess and then run it.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;using&lt;/span&gt; System;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;using&lt;/span&gt; System.Threading;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;namespace&lt;/span&gt; AnonMethods&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; Program&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;static&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;void&lt;/span&gt; Main(&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;string&lt;/span&gt;[]
args)&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;for&lt;/span&gt; (Int32
i &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; 0;
i &amp;lt; 20; i++)&lt;br&gt;
{&lt;br&gt;
Thread t &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;new&lt;/span&gt; Thread(&lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 11px; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: Courier New; BACKGROUND-COLOR: transparent"&gt;delegate&lt;/span&gt;()
{ Thread.Sleep(10); Console.WriteLine(i); });&lt;br&gt;
t.Start();&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
Thread.Sleep(5000);&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
}&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   We were playing with this and similar code in the experts area at the Ottawa VS launch
   yesterday. Fun, fun.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   My task ahead is to find a scenario that makes the subtleties of anonymous delegates
   useful. Anonymous delegates are certainly useful. It is the trick above with "i" that
   I'm talking about. I'll post in a couple days with more data on what is going on.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=20c75894-5947-4a62-a9c6-01b14516ecf8" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/AnonymousDelegates.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-11T09:51:50-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Ottawa VS 2005 Launch</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #003300; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana"&gt;Today marked the
   second of ten stops on the &lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/windowsserversystem/applicationplatform/launch2005/default.mspx"&gt;Canadian
   launch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = st1 ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:smarttags" /&gt; of
   VS 2005, in 
   &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;
      &lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;Ottawa&lt;/st1:City&gt;
   &lt;/st1:place&gt;
   . &lt;/span&gt;You can check out launch pics @ &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/tags/launch2005/"&gt;flickr&lt;/a&gt;.
   Looks like the pics are limited to Toronto at this point, but I expect that to change
   over the next few days.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   The Ottawa launch was another success. It was definitely more cozy than Toronto, being
   in a hotel, rather than a convention center. This different actually had its benefits.
   Faces started looking familiar more quickly and people didn't get lost ;)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   The ask the experts area was staffed by a bunch of the same experts as Toronto. By
   the second go, we definitely had our act together. For example, we did a better job
   of getting the best person to answer questions. I don't know a lot about databases
   or of our System.Data classes. Fortunately, &lt;a href="http://www.objectsharp.com/Bruce/"&gt;Bruce
   Johnson&lt;/a&gt; did, another .Net&amp;nbsp;expert from &lt;a href="http://www.objectsharp.com/"&gt;ObjectSharp&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   I managed to break away from the experts area for&amp;nbsp;a while to go see one of the
   talks. Gotta say that &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/jcarron/"&gt;Jerome&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.objectsharp.com/blogs/Barry/"&gt;Barry&lt;/a&gt; did
   a great job. &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/jbristowe/"&gt;John&lt;/a&gt; also did a great
   job during the keynotes. I didn't get to see him in action during the talks.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=01401e63-4355-4f77-9af4-bef9ca5b6a99" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/OttawaVS2005Launch.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-11T01:33:25-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Ottawa VS 2005 Launch T-1</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #003300; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana"&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = st1 ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:smarttags" /&gt;The 
   &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;
      &lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;Ottawa&lt;/st1:City&gt;
   &lt;/st1:place&gt;
   launch started with us arriving in town last night. 
   &lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;Ottawa&lt;/st1:City&gt;
   is one of my favourite cities in 
   &lt;st1:country-region w:st="on"&gt;Canada&lt;/st1:country-region&gt;
   , and certainly my favourite in 
   &lt;st1:State w:st="on"&gt;
      &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;Ontario&lt;/st1:place&gt;
   &lt;/st1:State&gt;
   . As a result, I was really looking forward to it. The trip started a little rough
   with a couple flights to 
   &lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;Ottawa&lt;/st1:City&gt;
   being cancelled and then me forgetting my jacket at gate 122 in 
   &lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;
      &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;Toronto&lt;/st1:place&gt;
   &lt;/st1:City&gt;
   airport. The dumb part is that they announced a lost jacket just before the plane
   left the gate (with everyone seated), but I was already deep into conversation with
   my two seat-mates. Anyway, a quick call to 
   &lt;st1:PlaceName w:st="on"&gt;Toronto&lt;/st1:PlaceName&gt;
   &lt;st1:PlaceType w:st="on"&gt;Airport&lt;/st1:PlaceType&gt;
   from 
   &lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;
      &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;Ottawa&lt;/st1:place&gt;
   &lt;/st1:City&gt;
   solved the problem after I was patched back through to gate 122. The jacket was there
   and we were good to go. My Swanndri jacket&amp;nbsp;is particularly important to me as
   I picked it up when Annie and I were married in 
   &lt;st1:country-region w:st="on"&gt;
      &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;New Zealand&lt;/st1:place&gt;
   &lt;/st1:country-region&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;
   five years ago.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
   &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;span style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #003300; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana"&gt;We drove from
   the airport to Microsoft 
   &lt;st1:country-region w:st="on"&gt;
      &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;Canada&lt;/st1:place&gt;
   &lt;/st1:country-region&gt;
   . We were late and were denied admittance at first by building security at Microsoft
   Ottawa. Note that the building has several tenants, so security was not MS-specific.
   Anyway, we explained the situation and got past that. Odd. We then spent the next
   hour with a bunch of local 
   &lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;
      &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;Ottawa&lt;/st1:place&gt;
   &lt;/st1:City&gt;
   .Net folks. We had some great conversations with the local developers over beer and
   cheese. I spent about 30mins talking with one guy in particular. We had a very interesting
   conversation about dynamic languages and some of the subtleties of anonymous delegates
   and methods in C#. I certainly knew about anonyomous delegates, but didn’t know about
   the subtleties that he mentioned. We talked more about the way that these work today
   at the launch and I now have a better idea. I’ll post more on this later.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
   &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
   &lt;font color=#000000&gt;After the beer and cheese, we headed to dinner with &lt;a href="http://www.objectsharp.com/Barry/"&gt;Barry
   Gervin&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href="http://www.objectsharp.com/"&gt;ObjectSharp&lt;/a&gt;. He's&amp;nbsp;the
   left-most guy in this &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/26606128@N00/61365570/"&gt;pic&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Definitely
   a very smart guy. He's a &lt;a href="http://barry.regionaldirector.ca/community/"&gt;regional
   director&lt;/a&gt; for&amp;nbsp;a bunch of Microsoft technologies&amp;nbsp;and also seems to like
   Italian food.&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img width="0" height="0" src="http://hoser.lander.ca/aggbug.ashx?id=9986ad61-2b6d-4a1d-bd52-e51b399198f5" /&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://hoser.lander.ca/OttawaVS2005LaunchT1.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-11T00:55:22-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
        </Items>
        <LoadedOK>true</LoadedOK>
      </feed>
      <children>
      </children>
    </LRSRSSTreeNode>
    <LRSRSSTreeNode>
      <feed>
        <URL>http://spaces.msn.com/members/manodesign/feed.rss</URL>
        <Title>Mano's Blog</Title>
        <Description>Design, 3D, Music, Sparkle, Avalon</Description>
        <PubDate>2006-03-20T13:02:00-05:00</PubDate>
        <Items>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>XBOX 360!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I finally got an XBOX 360! Let me tell you... It is an amazing console. The Live integration is excellent, and check out these Real Life / XBOX 360 comparison pictures (from Project Gotham Racing 3):&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.msxbox-world.com/forums/index.php?showtopic=3890"&gt;http://www.msxbox-world.com/forums/index.php?showtopic=3890&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;... speaks for itself!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;The funny thing is when people start communicating and chatting while playing (on Xbox Live, you have a headset with a microphone) - the other night one guy was singing The Beatles and some other guy was beat boxing some drums on top - classic! It can also be useful; this guy was going FAST and not hitting walls (!) in corners... I was able to ask a few questions and got some great tips on how to drive these crazy fast cars. The rich communication adds another dimension to a console. YES I know that it is not *new*, but the fact that it is centralized and so well integrated makes a world of difference compared to PC (and PS2) games with their separate services and inconsistent User Experience mechanisms across games.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+XBOX+360!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!542.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-18T11:26:37-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Windows Vista Digital Memory Experience</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.michaelgilmore.com"&gt;Mike Gilmore&lt;/a&gt;, a designer on my team has been working on the photo user experience in Vista. Details about what the team has been doing in this area has finally been &lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/windowsvista/experiences/memories.mspx"&gt;published on the web&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.microsoft.com/library/media/1033/windowsvista/images/experiences/memories_perfect_screen01.jpg"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Windows+Vista+Digital+Memory+Experience&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!537.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-08T13:50:40-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Live.com launches a new AJAX image search application</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A major update was launched today on Live.com. A big change is the addition of an AJAX-based image search interface. go to &lt;a href="http://live.com/"&gt;http://live.com&lt;/a&gt; and search for stuff.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;There are other changes, such as integration of Live Local, a bunch of new gadgets (Video gadget is nice), etc. It's basically an all-new, much better  Live.com.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.readwriteweb.com/archives/livecom_upgrade.php"&gt;Richard MacManus&lt;/a&gt; explains the details.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.readwriteweb.com/images/livecom_mar06b.png"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Live.com+launches+a+new+AJAX+image+search+application&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!534.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-08T13:38:35-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Why Windows Vista won't suck</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Extreme Tech has publishesd a must read article about the guts of Windows Vista. It is great to see details posted about the kernel, security, performance, SuperFetch, etc. I am looking forward to the much better audio experience, DX10's super fast performance and Geometry Shaders in action... oh, and the built-in speech-recognition.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;It is worth taking a few minutes to read the entire article:&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.extremetech.com/article2/0,1697,1931914,00.asp"&gt;http://www.extremetech.com/article2/0,1697,1931914,00.asp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Feel free to post comments and questions here. I can get the right folks to reply to them if needed.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Why+Windows+Vista+won't+suck&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!466.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-28T22:59:23-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Joining the Windows UX design team (MSX)!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Quick note to let everyone know that I am joining the Windows UX design team (MSX)!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;This is the team in charge of the User Experience of Windows, as well as many of the applications in and around Windows. I am still available to answer questions about Sparkle, since I worked on it for more than 4 years, although I will be focusing on Windows Vista ... and beyond!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Arial"&gt;What will I blog about? I will give you guys all the details about UI in Vista and about other cool projects I will be working on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Talking about Windows Vista, the latest AERO / Vista User Experience guidelines have been published!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/windowsvista/uxguide"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;http://msdn.microsoft.com/windowsvista/uxguide&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.microsoft.com/library/media/1033/windowsvista/images/features/feat_UX_01.gif"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.microsoft.com/library/media/1033/windowsvista/images/features/feat_wmp11.jpg"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Joining+the+Windows+UX+design+team+(MSX)!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!460.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-28T10:48:08-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Web designers and developers: don't miss the MIX conference</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://mix06.com/images/flair/buttons2.jpg"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://mix06.com"&gt;http://mix06.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Web+designers+and+developers%3a+don't+miss+the+MIX+conference&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!439.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-10T14:16:16-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Some of my music: Paysages 3</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Story&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;People often ask me if I could let them hear some of my music. I thought I'd pick one of the recent tracks I have worked on. Although I have been making music for many years, the ambient work I have done recently is what I feel has been the closest to my heart.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Paysages is my ambient album project. It comes from my passion for recordings I listened to while growing up: 70/80's ambient, with my own touches: dark, symphonic, descriptive. Working on this project makes me feel like when I was 4 years old, closing my eyes and listening to &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jean-Michel_Jarre"&gt;Jarre&lt;/a&gt;'s Magnetic Fields, Equinox, and &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mike_Oldfield"&gt;Mike Oldfield&lt;/a&gt; on my parent's turntable - in between synthesizer ambient records, I used to also listen to &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Le_Petit_Prince"&gt;Le Petit Prince&lt;/a&gt; over and over. &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;This is a ~6 minutes ambient track - there are a few parts to the track with &amp;quot;breaks&amp;quot; in between. You may think it is over when it is not. You will need to CRANK UP your volume to hear all the quiet passages and elements. Computer speakers may not produce all the frequencies accurately, so maybe plug some headphones in if that's the case. The goal was to produce in the flavors of old recordings, with headroom left where it is needed. You may notice that the timing on the notes played is not 100% mechanical/accurate. This is intentional. Basically my philosophy lately has been to &amp;quot;just play and record&amp;quot;. I believe that more of the emotions behind the notes are captured if one bypasses the &amp;quot;quantization&amp;quot; of midi sequencers. If something does not &amp;quot;feel&amp;quot; right, I simply record another take just as a guitarist or singer would. I'll note that I often end up liking a piece of recording even if it is technically incorrect. I base all my decisions on how I feel rather than on technique.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;I like to throw some little challenges here and there. This time I only used 1 instrument, the Poly Evolver Keyboard. In order to learn how to design sounds on it, I only used custom sounds for the Paysages 3 track. By this I mean that I did not pick sounds (patches) that were stored on the instrument and instead created each sound starting from a blank slate: a raw sawtooth oscillator, open filters, no envelopes defined, etc. Finally, &lt;strong&gt;no samples were used&lt;/strong&gt;: the &amp;quot;breathing&amp;quot; sounds are all produced in real time by designing a specific sound patch which sculpts the resulting signal coming from the noise generator on the instrument.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Listen&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Thanks everyone for listening! Music is a great vehicle for feelings, a powerful way to crystalize a specific moment in time. You can download a 64 kbps preview MP3 of Paysages 3 here: &lt;a href="http://www.manuelclement.com/m/assets/Paysages3.mp3"&gt;Paysages3.mp3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;-mano&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;ps: in french, Paysages means landscapes&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Some+of+my+music%3a+Paysages+3&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!431.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-08T19:04:48-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>The Register reviews Expression Interactive Designer</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regdeveloper.co.uk/2006/02/07/expression_interactive_designer/"&gt;http://www.regdeveloper.co.uk/2006/02/07/expression_interactive_designer/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+The+Register+reviews+Expression+Interactive+Designer&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!428.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-07T18:06:41-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Post questions about Expression Interactive Designer (formerly Sparkle)!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.microsoft.com/products/expression/en/_images/boxshot_main-ID.jpg"&gt; 
&lt;div&gt;Did you watch the &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/tags/Expression"&gt;channel 9 interviews&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Did you download the &lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/products/expression/en/interactive_designer/id_free_trial.aspx"&gt;Community Technology Preview&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Do you have questions? Post them here and I will do my best to answer them.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;-mano&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Post+questions+about+Expression+Interactive+Designer+(formerly+Sparkle)!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!417.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-06T15:25:17-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Wikiversity!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Don't miss this one... Go back to school via this great Wiki, on the Wikibooks site:&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/Wikiversity"&gt;http://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/Wikiversity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;MMhhh...&amp;quot;School of Mathematics&amp;quot;. &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikibooks/en/thumb/e/ed/Hypercube_star.png/300px-Hypercube_star.png"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Wikiversity!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!412.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-02T14:28:16-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Radio Controlled Rock Crawling!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Now... Tell me &lt;a href="http://www.orp.com.au/RC Madness/RC_01.wmv"&gt;this video &lt;/a&gt;doesn't make you want to drive some &amp;quot;real deal&amp;quot; &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Radio-controlled_car"&gt;RC cars&lt;/a&gt;!! Holy smokes...&lt;img src="http://spaces.msn.com/rte/emoticons/smile_tongue.gif"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;When I was 13, I had a Kyosho Inferno like &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Image:Inferno_rc.jpg"&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt;. I didn't drive it that much living in the city and having to take the bus for 1 hour everytime I wanted to use it, but it was cool... 1/8 scale 4x4 fuel-powered buggy... I had almost forgotten all about it.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;-mano&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Radio+Controlled+Rock+Crawling!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!403.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-28T10:35:15-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Zeldman on Web 3.0</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Read what Jeffrey has to say about AJAX, Ruby on Rails, being a &amp;quot;web designer&amp;quot;, going through the internet bubble, etc. I enjoyed it very much.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alistapart.com/articles/web3point0"&gt;http://www.alistapart.com/articles/web3point0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;-mano&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Zeldman+on+Web+3.0&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!401.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-27T16:30:28-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>New video interview with Channel 9!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/showpost.aspx?postid=157843"&gt;http://channel9.msdn.com/showpost.aspx?postid=157843&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+New+video+interview+with+Channel+9!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!389.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-24T11:59:11-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Expression Interactive Designer (formerly Sparkle) preview build is OUT!!!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don't know what this software is, &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=115387"&gt;watch the video interview on Channel 9&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Official website with auick video demos of key features, and links to install it: &lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/products/expression/en/interactive_designer/demos.mspx"&gt;http://www.microsoft.com/products/expression/en/interactive_designer/demos.mspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make sure to read the ReadMe.txt and take a look through the documentation, samples, tutorials.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Expect a TON of information on my blog! Stay tuned and &lt;a href="http://spaces.msn.com/members/manodesign/feed.rss"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;subscribe to my RSS feed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Feel free to post comments: questions, feedback, etc... I'll do my best to answer and will make sure to gather the feedback.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;-mano&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;PS: only minutes after this was online, Jered from RazorFish (top design house) &lt;a href="http://www.mindfury.com/blog/2006/01/expression-sparkle-interactive.html"&gt;posted his thoughts on EID here&lt;/a&gt;. He has been one of the early adopters.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;PS2: &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/ShowPost.aspx?PostID=157752"&gt;great forum thread posted on Channel 9&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a screenshot (click for full-size):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mano1.com/blog/files/EID_JanCTP.PNG"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mano1.com/blog/files/EID_JanCTP_small.png" border=0&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Expression+Interactive+Designer+(formerly+Sparkle)+preview+build+is+OUT!!!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!384.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-24T02:16:45-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Why do I need Windows Vista?</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;(edit: links *should* work now)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;OK so this post is brought to you by myself and... &lt;a href="http://scobleizer.wordpress.com/"&gt;Robert Scoble&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img src="http://spaces.msn.com/rte/emoticons/smile_wink.gif"&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Don't ask!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Expect more of these in the future; what I will do next is DIVE into some of these things, especially the AERO user interface and the new functionalities (improved copy+paste workflow, etc).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://spaces.msn.com/members/manodesign/feed.rss"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Subscribe to the RSS feed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to be notified when I post new Vista (and also Expression/Sparkle) stuff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.microsoft.com/library/media/1033/windowsvista/images/features/feat_UX_09.jpg"&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;font face=Tahoma size=3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why do I need Vista?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Let’s see...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;All new networking stack&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Many times the performance. &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=116349"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;All new audio stack&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Per-app audio, etc. &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=116347"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New UI and graphics layer&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Nicer UI with better video and audio integration.  &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=114694"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;(More details on this soon)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New search integration and file management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Tons of new things here. &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=114710"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New fonts and readability technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=146749"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New kernel changes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Performance, security, and all that. &lt;a href="https://mail.microsoft.com/exchweb/bin/redir.asp?URL=http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=148820"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New features for international users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;See Japanese and English fonts on screen at same time, etc. &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=146169"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New print technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=137532"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New installer technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=134577"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New sidebar and gadgets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Take advantage of that new high-resolution wide-screen monitor tech that’s now out. &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=128231"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New sideshow (external monitor for laptops)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Are you gonna buy a new laptop next year? It probably will have one of these. &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=124796"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New updated applications like Windows Mail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;Use email on your machine or answer questions in newsgroups? Watch this: &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=116711"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New crypto technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=116710"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New RSS platform&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=80533"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;New sound experience by Robert Fripp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;You gotta get Windows Vista if you want it. &lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=151853"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;Video&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Times New Roman" size=3&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robert Scoble continues:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;quot;And I still haven’t done many videos on the new security stuff, the new applications and games, the new Media Center stuff, the FAR improved handwriting recognition in Windows Vista’s tablet technology, and many other things... &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face=Arial color=navy size=2&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10pt;color:navy;font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Anyway, go ahead and stay on XP&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;img src="http://spaces.msn.com/rte/emoticons/smile_shades.gif"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.microsoft.com/library/media/1033/windowsvista/images/features/BoV_SyncCntr2.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Why+do+I+need+Windows+Vista%3f&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!362.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-22T01:19:03-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Video: meet Microsoft MAX</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You've seen me post about Microsoft MAX on my blog already, but this time you get to meet some people from the team. It is worth watching!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/showpost.aspx?postid=156065"&gt;http://channel9.msdn.com/showpost.aspx?postid=156065&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;-mano&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;table cellspacing="0" border="0"&gt;&lt;tr height="8"&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8opaELT_8J2ne6RPiV99hVU7F0NF0RNpbeVTWNSplGlupusExEcryX8bVz5FIXfdeCs852FXqiSpw9e6p76Z4DCdBhv0QTSZqbYM7t6b3ymgRyJywMphl-ds"&gt;&lt;img src="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8opaELT_8J2nezRgynebc-VFeyo5ZR0hpW6apnHCiCvc-jhSHy7llkeFXMwPvVK2jckvX7WzU424qTzmoNE3Dq8w" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td width="15"&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Video%3a+meet+Microsoft+MAX&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!361.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-19T11:18:34-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Pimp My Zen!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I dropped by &lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/stevewhitepsfd"&gt;Steve White&lt;/a&gt;'s office a few minutes ago. On his desk was his Zen music player - no plastic cover, circuit board exposed... I'm like &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Woah dude that's like... geek-hardcore!&amp;quot;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;img src="/rte/emoticons/smile_shades.gif"&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;I was convinced that he had *tricked* it out somehow. He explained that his headphone jack went bad and he couldn't unscrew the box without breaking some of the attachments. The coolest part is that he has wires hanging out of the unit with big soldering spots (see picture below) &lt;img src="/rte/emoticons/smile_omg.gif"&gt;. Duuude...&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Now, at this point I was &lt;strong&gt;almost &lt;/strong&gt;convinced that Steve was hardcore about his Zen, but the next thing he said did the trick for sure: he wrote and application which takes DVDs of conferences (like PDC) and extracts technical talks as files he can listen to on the Zen. &lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/windows/windowsmedia/howto/articles/audcdwme.aspx"&gt;He even wrote an article about it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mano1.com/blog/files/01-06-06_1610.jpg"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Pimp+My+Zen!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!356.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-06T19:36:02-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Nathan Dunlap on Media Center UI framework</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Today Nathan and I spent some time chatting about stuff and he was telling me about this UI Framework that is exposed by Media Center - there are already a few things built on it by MTV, Comedy Central, etc - and you can go make your own.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;You get all the high frame rate graphics and controls like the rest of the Media Center user interface... You can even use WPF (Avalon) with it.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Pretty cool! I don't own a Media Center so I haven't seen the stuff myself, but check out Nathan's blog for more details.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Link: &lt;a href="http://www.designerslove.net/2006/01/wpf-hits-big-screen.html"&gt;http://www.designerslove.net/2006/01/wpf-hits-big-screen.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.winsupersite.com/images/reviews/xpmce2005_06_sm.jpg"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Nathan+Dunlap+on+Media+Center+UI+framework&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!355.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-06T18:10:27-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>WinFX December CTP with... Cider editor!</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Grab the latest WinFX runtime, Visual Studio (or one of the free Express versions), and... Cider!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Cider is a visual editor for Avalon - it is NOT Expression Interactive Designer (Sparkle), as it is specifically made for developers (Sparkle is tuned for designers). Enjoy!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/windowsvista/getthebeta/default.aspx"&gt;http://msdn.microsoft.com/windowsvista/getthebeta/default.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;The link above has a list of various things to install to get you up and running.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;You can watch a video of Cider in action &lt;a href="http://download.microsoft.com/download/f/2/7/f2722c3f-963d-401a-a6f7-c026d7f1b08c/cider_2005.wmv"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;-mano&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+WinFX+December+CTP+with...+Cider+editor!&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!350.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-03T02:31:56-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>AJAX-style web development using the Atlas framework</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Quick post to get some folks updated on what MS is doing regarding AJAX-style web development.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;These days I am spending a lot of my spare time looking through what is out there - not just Microsoft's, but also things like Ruby on Rails :). It is important to look &amp;quot;all around&amp;quot; to ensure that we stay focused on building the best tools and platforms for you guys.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;We are working on a new AJAX-style Framework code-named &amp;quot;Atlas&amp;quot;. We are giving a preview of Atlas away on &lt;a href="http://atlas.asp.net/"&gt;http://atlas.asp.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://asp.net/images/atlaslogo.gif"&gt; 
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Atlas makes it easy to quickly build AJAX-style web applications: connect to web services, define UI interactions, data bind things together - without going through the pains of being on your own.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;If you want to be up to speed on what's happening, take a couple of hours to watch the presentations from the PDC conference: &lt;a href="http://microsoft.sitestream.com/PDC05/PRS/PRS312_files/Default.htm#nopreload=1&amp;amp;autostart=1"&gt;Part 1&lt;/a&gt; then &lt;a href="http://microsoft.sitestream.com/PDC05/PRS/PRS420.htm#nopreload=1&amp;amp;autostart=1"&gt;Part 2&lt;/a&gt; and install &lt;a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/vstudio/express/vwd/default.aspx"&gt;Visual Studio &amp;quot;Web&amp;quot; Express&lt;/a&gt; + &lt;a href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=52384"&gt;Atlas&lt;/a&gt; for free. Open the &lt;a href="http://atlas.asp.net/quickstart/default.aspx"&gt;Quickstart Tutorials&lt;/a&gt; and enjoy.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;I will try to find time (!) to play with Atlas on my end, and let you guys know how it goes.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Oh, and if you have any questions, &lt;strong&gt;feel free to post questions and feedback (even if negative) &lt;/strong&gt;and I will try to get someone from the Atlas team to look at them if I can't answer them directly.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Take care!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;-mano&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://asp.net/images/2screensLG.gif"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+AJAX-style+web+development+using+the+Atlas+framework&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;&lt;img style="position:absolute" alt="" width="0px" height="0px" src="c.msn.com/c.gif?NC=31263&amp;amp;NA=1149&amp;amp;PI=88469&amp;amp;RF=&amp;amp;DI=3919&amp;amp;PS=85545&amp;amp;TP=spaces.msn.com&amp;amp;GT1=manodesign%3b1033"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Blog/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!348.entry</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-28T13:09:20-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Photo Album: Sparkle</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sparkle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;table cellspacing="0" border="0"&gt;&lt;tr height="8"&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8opV4Lsp8ONizuqYhr5ZQw-9YT0oqzQDhGjo_1fCXqJwLXE2cv1jZAbJ7w1ExbHkRGVHfo1fSc3BuvIoffZzxO-XU0NUHzXdS19uIGlHWzw0vW98kZTZOs9A"&gt;&lt;img src="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8opV4Lsp8ONiz_1Ajfm4VICjjsgBK7a-QgXcOqDqFsVMj2BcSZXQB8V6lcg1oIX4dROFgcmcXd87UHEEbVLfd_Es" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Channel9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td width="15"&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8onDmmCCF1TEhzT3Lt7E8TbRytfLiDG7_h95n4U6sc8YNq99xM-DeJSCI9pO7BkgV3SUMgQs5FBOEUJ_zZ9_4-xtu3zf037VTKHpcBiBiALHC"&gt;&lt;img src="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8onDmmCCF1TEhwESEFMtfqXIRZqlNZI8zwzznb64nLOh-q71TJQZRAaVr5d5el9KxRt1JnVkza1W8i-0loH6kCc0" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;slashdot&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td width="15"&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8ojbqRqcSqiNK0Id0mkkh-aFtXzy5-ydhujxM_VmhlxljiR5M6sedfA5pUJnljA5jAf6HBV7o_ckh-euuSNoxVo5IIM5btQylnpIfMYVBxZOo"&gt;&lt;img src="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8ojbqRqcSqiNKqrW3qrS91ztw3nH5232DB-flo46qhaTIrnhWlp-YVdLvZHYQuZe_QPBlpoSVg5L9H25aiM-_92w" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;vectors_not_cartoony&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td width="15"&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8ovrOlG7m--GU6E5TRfkOexCuZ1El3ll9yYC_i7jleEvkou6TjX_A5SUTsuRBgNIID1CqDjfLTh4BRb_j0zdfOHRd1QJpLsYNJ260MDLHNOElFX967myybHk"&gt;&lt;img src="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8ovrOlG7m--GUfzXLDIrFTC08UIumaF64avk0Ptm2CfkS9KoT3R1wcZkGfA2dVBJ4fN0RMdZXavWxf8_zQhRQDKw" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;flashmagazine&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Photo+Album%3a+Sparkle&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/PersonalSpace.aspx?_c11_PhotoAlbum_spaHandler=TWljcm9zb2Z0LlNwYWNlcy5XZWIuUGFydHMuUGhvdG9BbGJ1bS5GdWxsTW9kZUNvbnRyb2xsZXI%24&amp;_c11_PhotoAlbum_spaFolderID=cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!156&amp;_c=PhotoAlbum</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-24T00:45:01-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Photo Album: PDC 2005 Tuesday</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;PDC 2005 Tuesday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;table cellspacing="0" border="0"&gt;&lt;tr height="8"&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8opWxFPE3_boKazzwMEhlJH5OzDGjqPHjLOZnpB4XgsBahzuUG7WTwUrKD8-wkK92VXVAWPlsxRwyC3a91HxzEv7C3HDwdvxl0fFzJB2bFqzk"&gt;&lt;img src="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8opWxFPE3_boKHPPnnWzo-3h0ezufgbtUXTBZJnkqbe0NIR-aInZtWowBPNAS0JWUNqgL4nhIOadM8ZSO8W5VDRU" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;PDC Banner&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td width="15"&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8ohavNrkYI9eXHSN2gfyFE0MJw2qBmogBDMqmR35aE5T5Z7Hmv7jWg0VLQQ_UOyNVxJkCcMvt0F7aDs--jz96cxpjrYzrtVWkfBlcgclHx7ta"&gt;&lt;img src="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8ohavNrkYI9eXv485UIw4F_NLbGDcTG1PuVNoGIyRlgfWu-EOoPdqzKJAjku7FeR_2C6_NK5Tm9ACT9h6LsnMWNo" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;MMhhh Vista Glass AERO UI&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td width="15"&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Photo+Album%3a+PDC+2005+Tuesday&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/PersonalSpace.aspx?_c11_PhotoAlbum_spaHandler=TWljcm9zb2Z0LlNwYWNlcy5XZWIuUGFydHMuUGhvdG9BbGJ1bS5GdWxsTW9kZUNvbnRyb2xsZXI%24&amp;_c11_PhotoAlbum_spaFolderID=cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!130&amp;_c=PhotoAlbum</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-15T03:08:22-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Photo Album: Pics</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;table cellspacing="0" border="0"&gt;&lt;tr height="8"&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8onScCVi_jAeg3R4NWvx-MTJtvqaCUOVkY8c69FH5WLzKfYBXMxCjc4zmhY6Oy-3f6AqFx2fzgfQogjeYIZEH0-AHdu7irOFpc4ftbVA4I8zN3tJGa8uaykQ"&gt;&lt;img src="http://tk.files.storage.msn.com/x1pM0jCSUoiRhDnthDZrYc8onScCVi_jAegNTvDQt2dWUed7HoOyv5kAVNQI_oxn8XMRyYFl3jJZwyo7IuYIhIiqkQRQBSTQyMM9TDTNn3CbqY" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;sk1_ad&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td width="15"&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+Photo+Album%3a+Pics&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/PersonalSpace.aspx?_c11_PhotoAlbum_spaHandler=TWljcm9zb2Z0LlNwYWNlcy5XZWIuUGFydHMuUGhvdG9BbGJ1bS5GdWxsTW9kZUNvbnRyb2xsZXI%24&amp;_c11_PhotoAlbum_spaFolderID=cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!117&amp;_c=PhotoAlbum</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-12T19:10:22-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Custom List: Friends and Colleagues</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Friends and Colleagues&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lynda.com"&gt;Lynda Weinmann&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.beingsmart.com"&gt;Christine Smart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/max"&gt;Microsoft MAX&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jonmeyer.com"&gt;Jon Meyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/brada"&gt;Brad Abrams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com"&gt;Channel 9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.designerslove.net/"&gt;Nathan Dunlap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/KamVedBrat"&gt;Kam VedBrat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/resources/design/"&gt;Microsoft Design&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.richardbanks.com"&gt;Richard Banks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/karstenj"&gt;Karsten Januszewski&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://spaces.msn.com/members/tjeerdh/"&gt;Tjeerd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.michaelgilmore.com"&gt;Mike Gilmore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.policarpo.us"&gt;Policarpo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://scobleizer.wordpress.com"&gt;Robert Scoble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.electronature.com"&gt;William Ngan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Lists/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!137</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-28T11:00:28-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Custom List: What I do</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;What I do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/products/expression/en/interactive_designer/default.mspx"&gt;Expression Interactive Designer (formerly Sparkle)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.manuelclement.com"&gt;My music: &amp;quot;Paysages&amp;quot; album (ambient)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mano1.com"&gt;Random Design Stuff (mano1.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/resources/design/"&gt;User Experience Designer at Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Lists/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!144</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-11T16:34:40-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Custom List: Expression Team Members</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expression Team Members&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.blois.us/blog/"&gt;Peter Blois&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://elementsofpassion.com"&gt;Amir Khella&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.samuelwan.com/information"&gt;Samuel Wan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/johngossman"&gt;John Gossman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/micahel"&gt;Michael Hunter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://scarynoises.com/blog/"&gt;Brad Becker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aisto.com/roeder/frontier"&gt;Lutz Roeder&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.secretrobot.com"&gt;Devon Strawn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.joemarini.com"&gt;Joe Marini&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/devi"&gt;Devindra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/stevewhitepsfd"&gt;Steve White&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://blogs.msdn.com/experiencematters"&gt;Christopher Lohr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/unnir"&gt;Unni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Lists/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!219</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-09T17:55:09-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Custom List: Important</Title>
            <Description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Important&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Important: This posting is provided &amp;quot;AS IS&amp;quot; with no warranties, and confers no rights.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://microsoft.sitestream.com/PDC05/TLN/TLNL10_files/Default.htm#nopreload=1&amp;amp;autostart=1"&gt;PDC 2005 talk: UI design using Sparkle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/downloads/details.aspx?FamilyId=FD380553-911E-4659-A085-4DD58AE4B9AE&amp;amp;displaylang=en"&gt;Vista (AERO) guidelines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=115387"&gt;Sparkle: video interview and demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/products/expression/en/interactive_designer/demos.mspx"&gt;Expression Interactive Designer: video overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/showpost.aspx?postid=157843"&gt;New Expression Interactive Designer (aka &amp;quot;Sparkle&amp;quot;) on Channel 9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;POST COMMENTS!! :)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://c.spaces.msn.com/CollectionWebService/c.gif?space=manodesign&amp;page=RSS%3a+&amp;referrer=" width=1 height=1 border=0 alt=""&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://spaces.msn.com/manodesign/Lists/cns!DC8DC039B51DE219!188</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-02T14:48:32-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
        </Items>
        <LoadedOK>true</LoadedOK>
      </feed>
      <children>
      </children>
    </LRSRSSTreeNode>
    <LRSRSSTreeNode>
      <feed>
        <URL>http://www.theinquirer.net/inquirer.rss</URL>
        <Title>the INQUIRER</Title>
        <Description>IT news - never knowingly undersoldered</Description>
        <PubDate>0001-01-01T00:00:00</PubDate>
        <Items>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Xbox 360 will be  a loser for Microsoft</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30453</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T19:04:23</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Speculation on handheld Xbox 360 grows</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30452</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T18:30:45</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Ageia offers physics support for Cell Playstation 3 chip</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30451</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T18:15:01</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Everywhere Girl goes to Ireland</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30450</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T16:43:33</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>June date for GameBoy Final Fantasy IV </Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30449</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T14:42:32</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Mechwarrior game designer appeals for cash</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30448</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T14:40:14</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Starforce DRM reboots your PC</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30447</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T14:38:32</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>XBox 360 back-up nearly there </Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30446</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T14:36:52</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Rambus says it will make more money</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30445</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T14:19:39</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>AMD takes off Athlon 64 X2 specs</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30444</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T14:06:41</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Prudential downgrades Intel</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30418</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T11:52:09</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Abit completes joint venture</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30443</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T11:23:27</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Take the INQ survey, win a Sony PSP handheld</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30442</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T10:59:57</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Microsoft to offer IP TV in Germany</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30441</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T10:41:29</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Google goes financial</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30440</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T09:50:44</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Geforce 7600 GS is 400 MHz G73</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30439</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T09:42:46</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Geforce 7300 won't do SLI</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30437</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T09:32:47</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>DRAM prices as flat as a flapjack</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30438</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T09:30:32</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Nvidia to launch 7300GT 256MB DDR2 </Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30436</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T09:22:24</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Nvidia SLI physics is a fat pipe dream</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30434</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T09:12:54</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Samsung intros solid state notebook drive</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30435</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T08:39:47</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>3.38GHz AMD X2 faces an Intel 2.93GHz Core Duo</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30426</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T08:28:27</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Paypal is outdated, Google should replace it</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30427</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T08:07:04</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Microsoft admits IE mess up</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30432</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T08:03:14</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Linux kernel 2.6.16 released</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30431</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T07:55:02</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>RIAA does not have godlike legal powers</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30428</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T07:53:55</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Amazon is anti-abortion,  claim</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30429</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T07:52:51</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Nanotubes headed for flat screen tellies</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30430</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T07:50:35</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Window XP does not melt Macs</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30433</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T07:48:29</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Dell drops da pricing bomb </Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30425</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T16:08:12</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Ballmer says Xbox  360 is "sort of" on-track</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30420</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T16:05:05</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Sid Meier plans sequels</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30419</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T16:03:37</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Microsoft helps Interpol with its inquiries</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30421</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T16:01:24</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Coppers say video game taunting led to killing</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30422</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T16:00:27</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Microsoft plans handhelds and iPod killer</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30423</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T15:58:46</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>AMD 'most admired' semiconductor company</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30417</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T15:00:41</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Dell 'talking to AMD'</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30415</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T15:00:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>ATI FireGL top end card reviewed</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30416</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T13:38:09</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Sound card scalpelled</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30414</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T11:17:15</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Nvidia shows off game physics GPU software</Title>
            <Description />
            <Link>http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=30413</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-20T11:10:40</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
        </Items>
        <LoadedOK>true</LoadedOK>
      </feed>
      <children>
      </children>
    </LRSRSSTreeNode>
    <LRSRSSTreeNode>
      <feed>
        <URL>http://news.com.com/2547-1_3-0-5.xml</URL>
        <Title>CNET News.com</Title>
        <Description>Tech news and business reports by CNET News.com. Focused on information technology, core topics include computers, hardware, software, networking, and Internet media.</Description>
        <PubDate>2006-03-21T17:00:09</PubDate>
        <Items>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>A chill in Oracle's hot numbers?</Title>
            <Description>Also: Laser chips could power petaflop computers.</Description>
            <Link>http://news.com.com/News.com+Extra/2001-9373_3-0.html?tag=rsspr.6052378</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T16:56:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Longhorn server still on track</Title>
            <Description>Blog: The latest delay of Windows Vista has no impact on the ship date for Windows Server "Longhorn," the server version of the operating...</Description>
            <Link>http://news.com.com/2061-10805_3-6052376.html?part=rss&amp;tag=6052376&amp;subj=news</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T16:53:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Vista delay is back to the future for Redmond</Title>
            <Description>Announcement won't help Microsoft shed the reputation that it's perennially late shipping products, says CNET News.com's Charles Cooper.</Description>
            <Link>http://news.com.com/2010-1016_3-6052365.html?part=rss&amp;tag=6052365&amp;subj=news</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T16:48:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title> Video: VW designs a car for your future</Title>
            <Description>Video: VW designs a car for your future. CNET executive editor Brain Cooley shows you a Volkswagen's
dashboard featuring programs and functions that mirror your
laptop computer or your Treo handheld.
 &lt;a href="http://news.com.com/1606-2-6052333.html?part=rss&amp;tag=6052333&amp;subj=news"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/ne/p/2006/videoplayer_vw.jpg" width="97" height="72" border="0" alt="Video: VW designs a car for your future" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://news.com.com/1606-2_3-6052333.html?part=rss&amp;tag=6052333&amp;subj=news</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T15:54:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>FBI ripped for IT upgrade costs</Title>
            <Description>Auditors criticize the agency for more than $17 million in "questionable contractor costs" and missing equipment.</Description>
            <Link>http://news.com.com/2100-1028_3-6052326.html?part=rss&amp;tag=6052326&amp;subj=news</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T15:54:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>More power for the video iPod</Title>
            <Description>Blog: I made the mistake of trying to watch "Dances With Wolves" on a plane headed to L.A. once. Of course, my player ran out of juice...</Description>
            <Link>http://news.com.com/2061-10801_3-6052289.html?part=rss&amp;tag=6052289&amp;subj=news</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-21T15:51:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
        </Items>
        <LoadedOK>true</LoadedOK>
      </feed>
      <children>
      </children>
    </LRSRSSTreeNode>
    <LRSRSSTreeNode>
      <feed>
        <URL>www.sysinternals.com/sysinternals.xml</URL>
        <Title>Sysinternals</Title>
        <Description>Advanced Windows Tools, Source Code and Information</Description>
        <PubDate>2006-03-07T16:47:13-05:00</PubDate>
        <Items>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>PsExec v1.71</Title>
            <Description>This version fixed a bug that sometimes caused the PsExec client to hang after running multiple times in quick succession.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/utilities/psexec.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-07T16:47:13-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Autoruns v8.5</Title>
            <Description>This new Autoruns release adds scanning of LSA security, notification, and authentication providers as well as Explorer protocol handlers and extensions. </Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/autoruns.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-07T16:46:57-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Mark to Speak at Microsoft TechEd 2006</Title>
            <Description>Mark is copresenting a preconference tutorial on advanced malware cleaning at TechEd US in Boston on June 11. In addition, he's delivering breakout sessions on topics including Vista kernel changes, troubleshooting with Filemon and Regmon, analyzing Windows crashes and hangs, Vista security changes, and advanced malware cleaning techniques.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Information/SpeakingSchedule.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-23T06:59:53-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Process Explorer v10.06</Title>
            <Description>This update includes a number of minor bug fixes (after the 10.0 release I quickly learned that people run Process Explorer with a vast array of diverse configurations).</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/ProcessExplorer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-23T06:57:33-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Process Explorer v10.02</Title>
            <Description>This major Process Explorer update has an extensive list of new features and enhancements aimed at usability and malware hunting. Just some of the examples include Runas and Run As Limited User commands, process restart, column sets, enhanced process tooltips for service-hosting and Rundll32 processes, working set breakdown columns, and DLL image verification and packed-image detection.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/ProcessExplorer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-08T16:00:47-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>RootkitRevealer v1.7</Title>
            <Description>This new RootkitRevealer release includes more sophisticated rootkit counter-measures, scanning of all Registry hives including user profiles, and numerous bug fixes.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/RootkitRevealer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-02T14:53:45-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Regdelnull v1.1</Title>
            <Description>In response to the use of such keys by malware, RegDelNull can now unlock and delete keys that not only have embedded nulls, but that also have security permissions that make them otherwise inaccessible.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/RegDelNull.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-13T18:42:25-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Sigcheck v1.3</Title>
            <Description>Sigcheck, a powerful command-line file version information and signature verification tool, now includes a new flag that has it only show a file's version number.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/Sigcheck.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-13T18:41:57-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>PsExec v1.7</Title>
            <Description>This PsExec update includes a new -l switch for use by administrative accounts to run processes with limited-user account privileges. Run a low-rights Internet Explorer before IE 7 comes out simply by creating a shortcut to launch it with the switch.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/PsExec.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-01-13T18:41:34-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Autoruns v8.43</Title>
            <Description>This update fixes several bugs and adds on-demand signature verification for individual items.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/autoruns.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-07T16:40:11-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>RootkitRevealer v1.6</Title>
            <Description>This version runs from Windows XP remote desktop sessions, includes a number of bug fixes and reduces the number of false positive descrepancies.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/RootkitRevealer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-07T16:39:54-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>PowerTools: PsLoglist</Title>
            <Description>Check out the December issue of Windows IT Pro Magazine for Mark's column where he tells you how to get the most out of PsLoglist (subscription required).</Description>
            <Link>http://www.windowsitpro.com/Windows/Article/ArticleID/48080/48080.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-07T16:39:42-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Inside Sony's Rootkit</Title>
            <Description>Mark dives into the technical details of Sony's rootkit implementation in the December issue of Virus Bulletin, the magazine for professional anti-malware researchers (subscription required).</Description>
            <Link>http://www.virusbtn.com/virusbulletin/archive/2005/12/index</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-12-07T16:39:05-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Four Sysinternals Tools Picked as Pricelessware 2006</Title>
            <Description>Filemon, Regmon, Process Explorer and Autoruns have been picked as the "best of the best" by alt.comp.freeware newsgroup participants.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.pricelesswarehome.org/2006/about2006PL.php</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-28T18:24:51-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>RegDelNull v1.0</Title>
            <Description>Use this new applet to find and delete Registry keys that are "undeleteable" by standard Registry-editing utilities because they have embedded null characters in their names.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/RegDelNull.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-28T18:24:31-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Autoruns v8.4</Title>
            <Description>This version of Autoruns adds enumeration of kernel-mode drivers, yet another attack vector being used by malware.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/autoruns.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-11-28T18:24:15-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Autoruns v8.31</Title>
            <Description>Fixes a bug in the KnownDLLs scan on 32-bit Windows.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/Autoruns.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-10-27T08:10:43-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Autoruns v8.3</Title>
            <Description>Another Autoruns update adds print monitor DLLs and Explorer column handlers - both of which have been used by real malware - and dramatically improves scan times when image verification is selected.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/Autoruns.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-10-26T11:33:02-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>RootkitRevealer v1.56</Title>
            <Description>This version adds support for NTFS volumes with cluster sizes larger than 4 KB.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/rootkitrevealer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-10-26T11:33:18-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>ProcFeatures v1.1</Title>
            <Description>This applet reports processor and Windows support for Physical Address Extensions and No Execute buffer overflow protection.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/procfeatures.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-10-26T11:34:05-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Autoruns v8.22</Title>
            <Description>This update corrects a bug in the compare feature.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/Autoruns.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-10-10T11:53:39-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Autoruns v8.21</Title>
            <Description>This Autorun update supports arbitrary length Registry and file system paths, adds a find capability to search through configured items, introduces a comparison feature to compare current autostarts with a previously saved version so that you can easily identify new additions, and knows about yet more autostart locations including the Winlogon boot verification Registry value and Shell open hijacks.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/Autoruns.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-10-06T18:44:58-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Power Tools: AccessEnum</Title>
            <Description>Mark's Power Tools column in the October issue of Windows IT Pro Magazine describes how to use AccessEnum to hunt down misconfigured Registry and file system security.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.windowsitpro.com/Article/ArticleID/47638/47638.html?Ad=1</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-10-06T18:45:14-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Mark's Interview with SearchWin2000.com</Title>
            <Description>In this interview Mark talks about Sysinternals, the most popular tools, and gives a brief introduction to an exciting upcoming tool.</Description>
            <Link>http://searchwin2000.techtarget.com/originalContent/0,289142,sid1_gci1131162,00.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-10-06T18:45:31-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Diskview v2.21</Title>
            <Description>This update fixes a bug that appears as a Diskview error dialog on certain volume configurations.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/DiskView.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-27T15:38:12-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Diskview 2.2</Title>
            <Description>Diskview, a utility that lets you look at the cluster allocations of a volume, now shows a summary of a file's fragments when you double-click on any of the file's clusters and the Show Next button navigates to the next fragment of a selected file.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/DiskView.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-23T10:42:50-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>PsExec v1.62</Title>
            <Description>PsExec no longer requires networking services to execute processes on the local system, including in the system account.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/utilities/pstools.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-23T10:41:55-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>PsExec v1.61</Title>
            <Description>This update fixes a bug when the -c switch is used.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/utilities/pstools.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-20T11:27:09-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>AccessEnum v1.32</Title>
            <Description>This update fixes a handle leak.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/AccessEnum.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-20T11:26:49-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Mark to speak at Microsoft IT Forum</Title>
            <Description>Join Mark in Barcelona in November for a preconference tutorial on Windows troubleshooting and breakout sessions on malware, crash and hang analysis and troubleshooting with Filemon and Regmon.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Information/SpeakingSchedule.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-15T11:06:44-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>DebugView v4.5</Title>
            <Description>After many user requests for the feature DebugView now has an option to create a new log file and clear the display each day.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/utilities/debugview.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-15T11:05:06-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>AccessEnum v1.3</Title>
            <Description>AccessEnum is a powerful security utilty that makes it easy to spot misconfigured file and Registry security descriptors. Version 1.3 includes bug fixes, Windows XP theming, and a new file format that's compatible with Excel importing.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/AccessEnum.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-09-07T11:04:27-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Livekd v3.0</Title>
            <Description>LiveKd, a utility that allows you to view the local system as if it were a crash dump using the standard Microsoft kernel debuggers, now supports x64 versions of Windows and includes some minor bug fixes.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/Livekd.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-30T14:41:11-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Regmon v7.02</Title>
            <Description>This minor update has clearer error messages for when an account does not have privileges required to run Regmon or Regmon is already running and consolidates the 32-bit and 64-bit (x64) versions into a single binary. It also fixed a bug where Regmon would sometimes not apply saved filter settings on startup.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/Regmon.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-28T19:54:34-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Filemon v7.02</Title>
            <Description>This update fixes an issue where Filemon would not apply saved filter settings on startup.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/Filemon.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-28T19:53:43-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Sysinternals Newsletter</Title>
            <Description>A new edition of the Sysinternals is out. Check out Wes Miller's guest editorial on running as non-admin, a list of tool updates since the last newsletter, and Mark's upcoming speaking schedule.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Information/SysinternalsNewsletter.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-24T14:29:05-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Process Explorer v9.25</Title>
            <Description>Several people have requested an option to use the old-style tray icon, which this version adds in the Options menu.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/ProcessExplorer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-22T15:34:44-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Process Explorer v9.23</Title>
            <Description>This update fixes an tray icon update bug.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/ProcessExplorer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-19T14:42:11-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Process Explorer v9.22</Title>
            <Description>Tweaks to the graph drawing and a Win9x bug fix mark this minor update.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/ProcessExplorer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-18T16:08:18-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Windows Internals Sample Chapter</Title>
            <Description>If you haven't bought a copy of Windows Internals and wonder what you might be missing check out the posted sample chapter, "Chapter 4: Management Mechanisms", which covers the Registry, Services, and WMI.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/WindowsInternals.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-18T15:34:19-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Process Explorer v9.2</Title>
            <Description>Process Explorer v9.2 shows a real-time CPU graph in its tray icon, adds CPU graph and I/O delta columns to the process view, reports 32-bit loaded DLLs for 32-bit processes on Windows 64-bit systems, and lets you view and edit process security descriptors. It also supports Windows Vista.</Description>
            <Link>http://www.sysinternals.com/Utilities/ProcessExplorer.html</Link>
            <pubDate>2005-08-16T11:48:54-04:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
        </Items>
        <LoadedOK>true</LoadedOK>
      </feed>
      <children>
      </children>
    </LRSRSSTreeNode>
    <LRSRSSTreeNode>
      <feed>
        <URL>blogs.msdn.com/brada/rss.aspx</URL>
        <Title>Brad Abrams </Title>
        <Description>Design Guidelines, Managed code and WinFX</Description>
        <PubDate>0001-01-01T00:00:00</PubDate>
        <Items>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Atlas talks at Mix06</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;If you are headed to &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href="http://mix06.com/"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#800080 size=2&gt;Mix06&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt; you will not want to miss the sessions on &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.asp.net/default.aspx?tabindex=9&amp;amp;tabid=47"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#800080 size=2&gt;Atlas&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;... Oh, and BTW, even if you are not going we are going to make a ton of this content available on &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.asp.net/default.aspx?tabindex=9&amp;amp;tabid=47"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#800080 size=2&gt;atlas.asp.net &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;and a few weeks after the show the sessions videos will be available to stream! &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Monday 3p:&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;NGW014 - Developing a Better User Experience with "Atlas"&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Shanku will show you in detail how to build a web 2.0 application using Atlas.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;If you are a developer building Ajax style apps, you don’t want to miss this talk.. It also sets a lot of context for the other talks in the series.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Tuesday 1:30p: NGW052 - Designing a Better User Experience with AJAX and "Atlas"&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Rick and I will talk about the principles of what makes a great Web 2.0 applications and how Atlas makes it easy to build.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;This is a very fun talk that will be good for BDMs, and Designers as well as developers because Rick is focused on the user experience today’s web applications need to bring and I am focused on how Atlas enables them.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Oh, and you will also see a little bit of a Vegas style business venture I am getting into for the demo ;-)&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Tuesday 3p:&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;NGW054 - Building an Application from Scratch Using ASP.NET 2.0&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;A href="http://weblogs.asp.net/scottgu"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#800080 size=2&gt;ScottGu&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt; will give an updated version of one of his best talks where he builds a very compelling web applications from scratch.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I remember hearing that onetime after he gave the talk someone came up to him and said he had just paid a contractor $50K+3 months to build that exact site that Scott had built in less than an hour!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;If you need a refresh on ASP.NET or just want a good show you should be there!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Wednesday 10a: NGW002 - Building Components and Services for the Programmable Web&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;If you are series about building an Ajax site you can’t miss &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.nikhilk.net/"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#800080 size=2&gt;Nikhil&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt; talk. &lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;He does an amazing job showing you how all this stuff works together.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I guarantee &lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;you will walk out of there wanting to build an app on Atlas.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;So only go if you have a little time on the plane ride home to build your own Mashup &lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;with Atlas.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;;-)&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;A few other ASP.NET sessions that I haven’t been as closely involved with but that look very compelling &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;NGW010 - Building an Interactive Community Platform with ASP.NET – Rob Howard is an excellent speaker and he should know something about the topic as his company leads the &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href="http://communityserver.org/default.aspx"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#800080 size=2&gt;Community Server&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt; project.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;NGW018 - Powering E-Commerce with PayPal&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;BTB007 - Building AJAX Applications Using Yahoo! Web Services&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;NGW038 - Overview of Live.com Gadgets&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;Oh and PS – Rick and I had the honor of being the very last &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=171314"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#800080 size=2&gt;Mix06 Buzz cast.. check it out. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: windowtext"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=554592" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/03/18/554592.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-18T14:59:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>16th Annual Jolt Awards -- Framework Design Guidelines and .NET Framework 2.0</Title>
            <Description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;I feel great about the recent &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://biz.yahoo.com/prnews/060317/sff036.html?.v=40"&gt;&lt;font color="#800080" face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Jolt awards&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt;... The two most close to home for me are:&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0321246756/bradabramsblo-20"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Framework Design Guidelines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt; book taking a &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://biz.yahoo.com/prnews/060317/sff036.html?.v=40"&gt;&lt;font color="#800080" face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Jolt Productivity award&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt;.. &lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;It is great to be recognized and to know that the book is meeting its goals: Help developers being wildly successful on our platform.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Oh, and I love the company we are in.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="/kcwalina/archive/2006/03/16/553433.aspx"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Krys mentions&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt; a few other past winners in the category.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; text-indent: -0.25in;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;·&lt;/font&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: 'Times New Roman'; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; font-size: 7pt; line-height: normal; font-size-adjust: none; font-stretch: normal;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F0201633612%2Fqid%3D1142654215%2Fsr%3D2-1%2Fref%3Dpd_bbs_b_2_1%3Fs%3Dbooks%26v%3Dglance%26n%3D283155"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Design Patterns&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt; by Erich Gamma, et al.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; text-indent: -0.25in;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;·&lt;/font&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: 'Times New Roman'; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; font-size: 7pt; line-height: normal; font-size-adjust: none; font-stretch: normal;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F1556155514%2Fqid%3D1142809235%2Fsr%3D2-1%2Fref%3Dpd_bbs_b_2_1%3Fs%3Dbooks%26v%3Dglance%26n%3D283155"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Writing Solid Code&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt; by Steve Maguire&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; text-indent: -0.25in;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;·&lt;/font&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: 'Times New Roman'; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; font-size: 7pt; line-height: normal; font-size-adjust: none; font-stretch: normal;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F0201544350%2Fqid%3D1142654307%2Fsr%3D1-1%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fs%3Dbooks%26v%3Dglance%26n%3D283155"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Object-Oriented Software Engineering: A Use-Case Driven Approach&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt; by Ivar Jacobson&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;If in a few years the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0321246756/bradabramsblo-20"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt;FDG&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt; &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;is still appearing in lists with those books I’ll be delighted!&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Time is the true test of any classic.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;BTW – I just heard that the FDG is in process of being translated to Chinese simplified and Korean!&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;I’ll of course note it here when they are available.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;The .NET Framework 2.0 is the Jolt Winner for the Libraries, Frameworks and Components category... &lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;I am very excited about this as it recognizes that we are making it easy for developers to write GREAT applications on our platform.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;I want to highlight another other winner in this category as well: &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dundas.com/home/index.aspx"&gt;&lt;font color="#800080" face="Arial"&gt;Dundas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt;... they have a great set of.NET controls that make our platform even better!&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;font color="#8f3b39" face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Maybe it is just my world view, but I think the success of the &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0321246756/bradabramsblo-20"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;FDG&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt; and the .NET Framework 2.0 share the same root.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;The common set of design guidelines and patterns that grew up and were conicallized with the .NET Framework are the real value of the FDG and help the make the .NET Framework a very useful tool for getting your job done.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;PS – Sorry &lt;/font&gt;&lt;a href="/kcwalina/"&gt;&lt;font color="#800080" face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Krys&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt; for being a little late on the news, I have been slammed on prep for MixO6... &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial; font-weight: normal;"&gt;Update: Klaus points out that I linked to the wrong
book... &lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;I linked to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: normal;"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F0735617228%2Fqid%3D1142654256%2Fsr%3D1-1%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fs%3Dbooks%26v%3Dglance%26n%3D283155"&gt;Writing
Secure Code&lt;/a&gt; rather than &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F1556155514%2Fqid%3D1142809235%2Fsr%3D2-1%2Fref%3Dpd_bbs_b_2_1%3Fs%3Dbooks%26v%3Dglance%26n%3D283155"&gt;Writing
Solid Code&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span style=""&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;As he mentions both are
great books... but fixed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial; font-weight: normal;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;span style="color: windowtext;"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial"&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 8pt; color: windowtext;"&gt;Posted from IE7 Beta2 Build 7.0.5335.0 &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=554258" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/03/17/554258.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-17T20:02:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>New CLR 2.0 book</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#8f3b39 size=2&gt;I just saw that &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=search-handle-url%2Findex%3Dbooks%26field-author-exact%3DJeffrey%2520Richter%26rank%3D-relevance%252C%252Bavailability%252C-daterank"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial size=2&gt;Jeff Richter’s&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;&lt;FONT color=#8f3b39&gt; &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;B style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal"&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F0735621632%2Fqid%3D1142137863%2Fsr%3D1-1%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fs%3Dbooks%26v%3Dglance%26n%3D283155"&gt;CLR via C#&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;FONT color=#8f3b39&gt; is in stock on Amazon.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;This is an update to his very popular &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F0735614229%2Fqid%3D1142137906%2Fsr%3D1-2%2Fref%3Dsr_1_2%3Fs%3Dbooks%26v%3Dglance%26n%3D283155"&gt;Applied Microsoft .NET Framework Programming&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#8f3b39&gt; and it covers a bunch of new goodies in CLR 2.0... &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#8f3b39 size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;&lt;FONT color=#8f3b39&gt;I gotta say I love the title change... &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;B style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal"&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F0735621632%2Fqid%3D1142137863%2Fsr%3D1-1%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fs%3Dbooks%26v%3Dglance%26n%3D283155"&gt;CLR via C#&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT color=#8f3b39&gt; &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;FONT color=#8f3b39&gt;is one of the shortest tech book titles I have seen... Oh course that is coming from the guy who came up with &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;path=ASIN%2F0321154894%2Fref%253Dpe%255Fsnp%255F894"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Standard Library Annotated Reference Volumes 1: &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: Verdana; mso-bidi-font-weight: bold"&gt;Base Class Library and Extended Numerics Library&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#8f3b39&gt;and &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?link_code=ur2&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;tag=bradabramsblo-20&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;path=tg/detail/-/0321194454/qid=1123732503/sr=1-1/ref=sr_1_1?v=glance%26s=books"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Volume 2: &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: Verdana; mso-bidi-font-weight: bold"&gt;Networking Library, Reflection Library, and XML Library&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#8f3b39&gt; &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#8f3b39&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;;-)&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#8f3b39 size=2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;&lt;FONT color=#8f3b39&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial&gt;Enjoy!&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=549740" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/03/11/549740.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-11T20:36:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Webcast on Atlas...</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;I just noticed that &lt;A HREF="/jhawk/archive/2006/03/07/545827.aspx"&gt;Jonathan Hawkins posted&lt;/A&gt; a great &lt;A href="mms://wm.microsoft.com/ms/uifx/ATLAS_Technology%20Preview_2-27-06.wmv"&gt;new webcast covering the basics of Atlas&lt;/A&gt;... You will get benefit from this webcast whether you are a longtime ASP.NET head wanting to easily leverage the power of Web 2.0 with the Atlas server side model (UpdatePanel and fiends) or a die-hard Web 2.0 hacker who wants to push the envelop in terms of what you can do with Ajax by using the Atlas client side framework.&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;Let me hear what you think&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;Enjoy!&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=546857" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/03/08/546857.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-08T21:02:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>WinForms, WPF and Working for Microsoft</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;I had an interview candidate ask me recently what I loved most about working for Microsoft.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Oddly enough the answer is you!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I love the amazing community of developers Microsoft is fortunate enough to have.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I love it that you let us know when things aren’t work the way they should and I really, really love it when we can fix those things right away.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Mike talked about one of those things in &lt;A HREF="/mhendersblog/archive/2006/03/01/541422.aspx"&gt;his recent post on shipping the WPF-WinForms&lt;/A&gt; interop technology in Vista\WinFX.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Having been somewhat involved in making that decision, I can tell you that feedback from YOU played a key role in making the change... So please, by all means, keep the feedback coming and thank you!&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=541826" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/03/02/541826.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-02T08:58:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Dr. Dobbs on the Framework Design Guidelines</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/B000060MI5/bradabramsblo-20/"&gt;Dr. Dobbs&lt;/A&gt; Bookshelf reviews the &lt;A href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0321246756/bradabramsblo-20"&gt;Framework Design Guidelines&lt;/A&gt; in the &lt;A href="http://www.ddj.com/articles/2006/0604/"&gt;current issues&lt;/A&gt;.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;I appreciate the fact that Peter notes that the book is good for people learning the.NET Framework as well as those designing their own libraries.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;While we did specifically target the book for folks building libraries, it has been my experience that LOTs of developers can find value in the book... Knowing the rules to the system help you understand the system.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;Oh, and Peter even if they are utopian views, I hope the book is in some small way life changing and I sure hope it settles some newsgroup disputes ;-) &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; LINE-HEIGHT: 12pt; mso-margin-top-alt: auto; mso-margin-bottom-alt: auto"&gt;&lt;I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 8.5pt; COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-bidi-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;Dr. Dobb's Journal&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 8.5pt; COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-bidi-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;, April 2006&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 13.5pt; COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-bidi-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-font-kerning: 18.0pt"&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.ddj.com/documents/s=10035/ddj0604j/0604j.html"&gt;Framework Design Guidelines&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-bidi-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;By Peter N. Roth&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 8.5pt; COLOR: black; FONT-FAMILY: Verdana; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-bidi-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;Thanks for the review!&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=541803" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/03/01/541803.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-01T20:05:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Windows Vista and Windows Forms</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Folks on the &lt;A href="http://www.windowsforms.net/"&gt;Windows Forms&lt;/A&gt; team are working hard to make sure Windows Forms applications look great on Vista, but we can always use your help in the real world apps you are using.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I know many of you MSDN subscribers &lt;A href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/windowsvista/"&gt;have picked up the Vista CTPs&lt;/A&gt; and tried your own Windows Forms apps on it.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;We’d love to hear your feedback on how it went.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Did the functionality work?&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Did it look right? Did it feel like a &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = st1 ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:smarttags" /&gt;&lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;Vista&lt;/st1:place&gt; era application?&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Please comment here or &lt;A HREF="/brada/contact.aspx"&gt;drop me a line&lt;/A&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=541094" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/03/01/541094.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-03-01T08:42:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>ClickOnce and Permission Elevation </Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;A href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/msdnmag/issues/04/05/ClickOnce/"&gt;ClickOnce&lt;/A&gt; is a very cool client application delivery system that we shipped in V2.0 of the .NET Framework and that WPF (aka Avalon) makes use of as well.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Before we even shipped V1.0 of the .NET Framework we have know that deployment is the key issue for client applications.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;No mater how good the UI framework is if the app can’t be deployed it is useless.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;While ClickOnce doesn’t solve all deployment (machine provisioning for example) it does make HUGE steps towards delivering web style deployment of client applications.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;I really appreciate &lt;A href="http://www.leastprivilege.com/CommentView.aspx?guid=dd4eda16-f930-44e0-9f4e-56cfa0cda3f4"&gt;the feedback&lt;/A&gt; we have gotten recently on ClickOnce around &lt;A href="http://msdn2.microsoft.com/en-us/library/01daf08f.aspx"&gt;Permission Elevation&lt;/A&gt;... One of the things a love about working on this technology is that we have such a great community that is active about telling us what they like and don’t like.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;In response to the feedback, &lt;A HREF="/saurabh/archive/2006/02/28/540878.aspx"&gt;Saurab posted some more information&lt;/A&gt; about what went into our thinking around this decision... I’d love to hear your feedback and reaction... Just using his blog for comments is goodness or feel free to &lt;A HREF="/brada/contact.aspx"&gt;email me directly&lt;/A&gt;.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=541028" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/02/28/541028.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-28T19:51:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Slashdot on Framework Design</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Very cool to see &lt;A href="http://ask.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=06/02/24/0148201"&gt;Slashdot address framework design&lt;/A&gt;, although I am a bit disappointed they didn't reference the &lt;A id=bp___v___bs___lcl___Categories__ctl0_Links__ctl1_Link href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0321246756/bradabramsblo-20"&gt;&lt;FONT color=#4271d6&gt;Framework Design Guidelines &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;as it covers all of these areas.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I do basically agree with the primary point of the post... &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;Our presumption is that software developers mostly evaluate following software framework characteristics based on:&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt; &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;OL type=1&gt;
&lt;LI class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1; mso-margin-top-alt: auto; mso-margin-bottom-alt: auto; tab-stops: list .5in"&gt;&lt;I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;perceived ease of use (e.g. easy to learn, easy to adapt)&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt; &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;
&lt;LI class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1; mso-margin-top-alt: auto; mso-margin-bottom-alt: auto; tab-stops: list .5in"&gt;&lt;I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;perceived usability (e.g. improving developer performances, reducing work, faster development),&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt; &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;
&lt;LI class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1; mso-margin-top-alt: auto; mso-margin-bottom-alt: auto; tab-stops: list .5in"&gt;&lt;I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;perceived sustainability (e.g. perceived long term support, supporting standards, clear project directions) and&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt; &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;
&lt;LI class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1; mso-margin-top-alt: auto; mso-margin-bottom-alt: auto; tab-stops: list .5in"&gt;&lt;I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;perceived fit to specific developer requirements (e.g. suited language, suited functions, suited architecture).&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Times New Roman'; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt; &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/LI&gt;&lt;/OL&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;And it is interesting that this not only goes to base frameworks (Java, .NET Framework, etc) but also to the frameworks you design for your own internal usage.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Are they easy learn, usable, sustainable and appropriate for the audience?&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Are there any other characteristics that you use to chose a framework?&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=539205" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/02/25/539205.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-25T10:16:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>PM Tip #21: Sanity Will Prevail </Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;One of the core jobs of a PM is to hold tight to the vision of the product.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;There are a million things that can distract you and set you back.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Features get cut, resources get moved, partners fail to deliver.. the list goes on and on.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Many of these things are within your control and you should do everything you can to make those things come out right.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;But let’s face it, there are also a number of things that are outside of your control.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;You can chime in, raise the red flag and point out the issues but at some point your authority stops... so what do you do then?&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Well, first it is important to make sure you are indeed leading the right vision.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Have market conditions changed, have customer requirements or technology changed?&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Don’t be afraid to revisit even deeply held believes... But if after revisiting you still buy into the vision...&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Well, then there are really only two options.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Option one is sulk and say the system screwed you and option 2 to believe that sanity will eventually prevail and continue to work toward that great day.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Option one (the sulking) is toxic to the team... it not only under-minds the area in question, but the whole product.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;If you are really it this camp it is time to find a new job.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Option two (sanity will prevail) may very well seem pointless.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I mean after all these are issues where you have no control over.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;However, I am firmly convinced that if enough smart people are following this path and continue to work toward that great day it is bound to happen sooner or later.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;Plus, the world is a much better place with hope rather than sulking.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;So even if the full vision never happens at least you had a good time working towards it. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = st1 ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:smarttags" /&gt;&lt;st1:PersonName w:st="on"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;A HREF="/davidtr"&gt;David Treadwell&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/st1:PersonName&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;, one of the best leaders I have had an opportunity to work with once told me in a case like that that "Sanity Will Prevail".&amp;nbsp; While there were times I doubted it along the way he ended up being right and his positive attitude around a hard issue was key to making the team work.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;So, next time a “stupid” decision gets made rather than sulking about it, re-examine your case honestly then if you still believe in the vision tell yourself (and others) that sanity will prevail then go work towards making sure it does.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=536644" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/02/22/536644.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-22T05:54:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>PM Tip # 32: Nothing kills excitement like ambiguity   </Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;As a PM, one of your key jobs is building excitement for your feature.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;This excitement is important among many different audiences.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndentCxSpFirst style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;·&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Among potential customers for your feature – Customers rarely buy or adopt what they are not excited about.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndentCxSpMiddle style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;·&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Within your feature team – People do better when they are working on something they love.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Help your team mates find that thing to love. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndentCxSpMiddle style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;·&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Up your management chain – Make sure your manager (and their manager) is equally excited about your feature.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;This pays dividends later when you need them to help you remove roadblocks for you.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndentCxSpLast style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;·&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Throughout your partners – Likely there are a number of partners that are helping to deliver on the end-to-end value of the feature.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Getting them excitement ensures the core value will shine through.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;I am sure all that is motherhood and apple pie... What is interesting is how to create that excitement.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;While there is a &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = st1 ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:smarttags" /&gt;&lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;LOT&lt;/st1:place&gt; to say on that topic, let me just touch on one element.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;A href="http://vicgundotra.com/"&gt;Vic Gundotra&lt;/A&gt;, one of the best product evangelists I have ever worked with once told me:&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; TEXT-INDENT: 0.5in"&gt;&lt;I style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 11pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-bidi-font-size: 10.0pt"&gt;“Nothing kills excitement like ambiguity”&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;How true that is!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;The sort of “but, but, and, and” kind of language we are trained to use as engineers does not help in building excitement.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Certainly there is a role for preciseness of language in product specifications (where to be frank we don’t have enough of it).&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;It is way harder to have a clear, correct, simple language than ambiguous speech.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;But the work is worth it.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;If you can work toward getting a clear 10 word description of the excitement thing about your project you are well on the way to achieving it! &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;I’d love to compile a list of excitement killing ambiguity or excitement generating clarity.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Please send them to me or comment here with your examples!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=535235" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/02/21/535235.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-21T06:46:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Video plug for Atlas talk at Mix...</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;A href="http://weblogs.asp.net/shankun"&gt;Shanku&lt;/A&gt;, &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;A href="http://weblogs.asp.net/bleroy/"&gt;Bertrand Le Roy&lt;/A&gt; and I recently &lt;A href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=163508"&gt;shot a spot about our Atlas\Ajax&lt;/A&gt; presence at &lt;A href="http://mix06.com/"&gt;Mix&lt;/A&gt;... I’d love to hear thoughts... what would you like to hear us cover?&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;Here is a list of the breakouts that are directly &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = st1 ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:smarttags" /&gt;&lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;&lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;Ajax&lt;/st1:place&gt;&lt;/st1:City&gt; focused... There is also some good information in the keynotes. &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Developing a Better User Experience with "Atlas"&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Speaker(s): Scott Guthrie&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Focus(s): Developer&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Session Type(s): Breakout&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;This session is a developer overview of "Atlas", Microsoft's new cross-platform/cross-browser framework for building rich, client-centric AJAX-style Web applications. Learn about data-binding, modernized object-oriented JavaScript techniques, and designing interactive UI, as you follow along through the construction of a mash-up&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Designing a Better User Experience with &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;&lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;AJAX&lt;/st1:City&gt;&lt;/st1:place&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Speaker(s): Brad Abrams, Rick Spencer&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Focus(s): Designer&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Session Type(s): Breakout&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;This session explores best practices for designers who are tackling the real challenges of building AJAX-style user experiences on the Web. Learn about designing richer user experiences directly from the Windows Live Local and "Atlas" development teams. Explore how the "Atlas" controls and components remove the complexity from designing rich, interactive experiences, and help you build AJAX-style applications more quickly.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Building Components and Services for the Programmable Web&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Speaker(s): Nikhil Kothari&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Focus(s): Architect, Developer&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Session Type(s): Breakout&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Want to learn how to expose components and services like Windows Live Local and Virtual Earth, but not sure where to begin? This session introduces real-world design patterns and best practices for constructing reusable Web components and Web-based services for the programmable Web. Explore how "Atlas" makes it incredibly simple for developers to consume these components and services to build gadgets, mash-ups, and other rich user experiences on the Web. Learn how to deliver functionality for a new generation of Web applications designed around reusable UI, components, and Web-based services.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Lessons from the Trenches: Engineering Great &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;&lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;AJAX&lt;/st1:City&gt;&lt;/st1:place&gt; Experiences&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Speaker(s): Scott Isaacs&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Focus(s): Designer, Developer&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Session Type(s): Breakout&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Explore the challenges and lessons learned developing the Windows Live and Gadgets Web client frameworks powering Windows Live, Hotmail (Kahuna beta), Spaces, and more. This technical talk presents design and architectural considerations for building interactive AJAX-like sites. See how componentization, network management, accessibility, page composition, and more impact the design and engineering of your Web application.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Overview of Live.com Gadgets&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Speaker(s): Sanaz Ahari&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Focus(s): Business Decision Maker, Designer, Developer&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Session Type(s): Breakout&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Live.com, the front-door to Windows Live, enables users to consume and manage their services in one place using gadgets. Learn about the benefits of live.com, the use of &lt;st1:City w:st="on"&gt;&lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;AJAX&lt;/st1:place&gt;&lt;/st1:City&gt; and "Atlas" for building rich gadgets, and reaching Windows Live customers by building gadgets.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;BTW – other good &lt;A href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Showforum.aspx?forumid=14&amp;amp;tagid=91"&gt;Mix06 videos are posted as well&lt;/A&gt;. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=535509" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/02/20/535509.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-20T08:27:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Ajax for the rest of us:  Atlas, the profile store and web based forms</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;While &lt;A href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/AJAX"&gt;Ajax&lt;/A&gt; is getting lots of &lt;A href="http://www.live.com/#q=Ajax%20development&amp;amp;scope=1&amp;amp;first=1"&gt;buzz&lt;/A&gt; in the new &lt;A href="http://www.technorati.com/tag/Web%202.0"&gt;Web 2.0 style applications&lt;/A&gt; it enables I was struck recently by the impact this programming style could have on possibly the most popular web application: web based forms!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;I hate filling out web forms, in fact one of the only things I hate worse than filling out web forms is doing it twice!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Several times recently I&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;have been in the middle of filling out a form and lost all by work.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;There are several reasons for it: &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;1. Hitting back button to find some data&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;2. clicking on a link which navigates the browser to another place&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;3. timing out on the server&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;4. the ups and downs of wi-fi&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;If any of these (or many other) common things happen, you have to restart fillout the form.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Argg!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I certainly understand that the website only wants forms that are complete for data integrity reasons, but surely something could be done!&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;A href="http://atlas.asp.net/"&gt;Enter Atlas&lt;/A&gt;... As you may know Atlas is an extension to &lt;A href="http://www.asp.net/"&gt;ASP.NET 2.0&lt;/A&gt; that makes Ajax style development super easy.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;With Atlas + the &lt;A href="http://www.ondotnet.com/pub/a/dotnet/2004/10/25/libertyonwhidbey.html"&gt;profile store&lt;/A&gt; offered in ASP.NET 2.0 it is very easy to build a much more user friendly form. Clearly there is some network\server load for this which could be optimized down via a timer on the client if the load becomes an issue.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;However the nice thing about this style is that there is no user visible delay as everything is done asynchronously. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;My goal was to store form data asynchronously on the server in a per user state cache as it typed in. And then reload it from the server (again, asynchronously) if the user navigates away and then back to this page.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;This allows the user’s data to be sticky.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;The profile service works with any sort of authentication scheme, here I am using NTLM.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;This doesn’t show up in the code below at all and works equally well with a more traditional user name and password system.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Just install the &lt;A href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=52384"&gt;Jan Atlas bits&lt;/A&gt;, open a new atlas web site and try these few easy steps... &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-fareast-font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;1.&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Update web.config with the schema of the data you want to store. Here is what my section looks like:&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;profile&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;properties&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 3"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;add&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;name&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;Name&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;defaultValue&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;""&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;allowAnonymous&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;true&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;add&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;name&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;Address1&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;defaultValue&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;""&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;allowAnonymous&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;true&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;add&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;name&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;Address2&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;defaultValue&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;""&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;allowAnonymous&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;true&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;add&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;name&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;City&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;defaultValue&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;""&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;allowAnonymous&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;true&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;add&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;name&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;State&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;defaultValue&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;""&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;allowAnonymous&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;true&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;add&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;name&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;Zip&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;defaultValue&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;""&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;allowAnonymous&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;true&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;add&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;name&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;Country&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;defaultValue&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;""&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;allowAnonymous&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;true&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;add&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: red; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;name&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;Phone&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;defaultValue&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;""&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;allowAnonymous&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;=&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;true&lt;/SPAN&gt;"&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;properties&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: maroon; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;profile&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-fareast-font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;2.&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;The labels and textboxs&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;to your ASPX page.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Notice I set a client side on change event on the textbox&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;tr&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;td&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;td&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;td&lt;/SPAN&gt; &lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;style&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;="width: 24628px; text-align: right;"&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;strong&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;Full Name:&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;strong&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt; &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;td&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;td&lt;/SPAN&gt; &lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;style&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;="width: 378px"&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;input&lt;/SPAN&gt; &lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;type&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;="text"&lt;/SPAN&gt; &lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;id&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;="txtName"&lt;/SPAN&gt; &lt;SPAN style="COLOR: red"&gt;onchange&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;="onNameChange()"/&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;td&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;tr&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;I only show one here, you will need to do the others.. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-fareast-font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;3.&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Do a little setup work to make it easier to deal with the html elements on the page in Jscript&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;var&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt; txtName = document.getElementById(&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;'txtName'&lt;/SPAN&gt;);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;var&lt;/SPAN&gt; txtAddress1 = document.getElementById(&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;'txtAddress1'&lt;/SPAN&gt;);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;var&lt;/SPAN&gt; txtAddress2 = document.getElementById(&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;'txtAddress2'&lt;/SPAN&gt;);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;var&lt;/SPAN&gt; txtState = document.getElementById(&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;'txtState'&lt;/SPAN&gt;);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;var&lt;/SPAN&gt; txtCity = document.getElementById(&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;'txtCity'&lt;/SPAN&gt;);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;var&lt;/SPAN&gt; txtZip = document.getElementById(&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;'txtZip'&lt;/SPAN&gt;);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;var&lt;/SPAN&gt; txtCountry = document.getElementById(&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;'txtCountry'&lt;/SPAN&gt;);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;var&lt;/SPAN&gt; txtPhone = document.getElementById(&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: maroon"&gt;'txtPhone'&lt;/SPAN&gt;);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-fareast-font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;4.&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;When selection leaves the text box, the on change event is raised.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Here we need to store the value of the textbox into the local profile store.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;It will refresh the server asynchronously.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;This is where the magic of Atlas comes in.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Web.Profiles is part of the client side Atlas Jscript framework&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;function&lt;/SPAN&gt; onNameChange () {&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Web.Profile.properties.Name = txtName.value;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Web.Profile.save();&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;}&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormalIndent style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in; TEXT-INDENT: -0.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-fareast-font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-list: Ignore"&gt;5.&lt;SPAN style="FONT: 7pt 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;On page load we need to restore any user state that we have stored from last time.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;To do this we define two client side Jscript methods.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;One is called when the page is loaded, the other is called, you guessed it, asynchronously once the profile data has been retrieved from server.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;function&lt;/SPAN&gt; OnPageLoad() {&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Web.Profile.loaded.add(onProfileLoadComplete);&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Web.Profile.load(); &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;}&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: green"&gt;//Called when the profile data has been loaded from the server&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="COLOR: blue"&gt;function&lt;/SPAN&gt; onProfileLoadComplete()&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;{&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;txtName.value = Web.Profile.properties.Name;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;txtAddress1.value = Web.Profile.properties.Address1;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;txtAddress2.value = Web.Profile.properties.Address2;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;txtCity.value = Web.Profile.properties.City;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;txtState.value = Web.Profile.properties.State;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;txtZip.value = Web.Profile.properties.Zip;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;txtCountry.value = Web.Profile.properties.Country;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;txtPhone.value = Web.Profile.properties.Phone;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;}&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Here is the resulting app -&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;notice the XmlHttp callbacks listed in the &lt;A href="http://www.nikhilk.net/Project.WebDevHelper.aspx"&gt;Web Development Helper&lt;/A&gt; I have installed... &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: blue; FONT-FAMILY: 'Courier New'; mso-no-proof: yes"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-tab-count: 1"&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = v ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" /&gt;&lt;v:shapetype id=_x0000_t75 coordsize="21600,21600" o:spt="75" o:preferrelative="t" path="m@4@5l@4@11@9@11@9@5xe" filled="f" stroked="f"&gt;&lt;v:stroke joinstyle="miter"&gt;&lt;/v:stroke&gt;&lt;v:formulas&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="if lineDrawn pixelLineWidth 0"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="sum @0 1 0"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="sum 0 0 @1"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="prod @2 1 2"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="prod @3 21600 pixelWidth"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="prod @3 21600 pixelHeight"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="sum @0 0 1"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="prod @6 1 2"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="prod @7 21600 pixelWidth"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="sum @8 21600 0"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="prod @7 21600 pixelHeight"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;v:f eqn="sum @10 21600 0"&gt;&lt;/v:f&gt;&lt;/v:formulas&gt;&lt;v:path o:extrusionok="f" gradientshapeok="t" o:connecttype="rect"&gt;&lt;/v:path&gt;&lt;o:lock v:ext="edit" aspectratio="t"&gt;&lt;/o:lock&gt;&lt;/v:shapetype&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;A href="/photos/brada/images/534605/original.aspx" target=_blank&gt;&lt;IMG src="/photos/brada/images/534605/548x480.aspx" border=0&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;I can now, without hitting submit, close the browser, navigate away from the page and back – or even open it up the page in a different browser, on a different machine and my data is till saved! &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;A href="/photos/brada/picture534605.aspx" target=_blank&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;A href="/photos/brada/images/534606/original.aspx" target=_blank&gt;&lt;IMG src="/photos/brada/images/534606/611x480.aspx" border=0&gt;&lt;/A&gt; 
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Update 1: While going through the fun of uploading and attaching pictures via Community Server I just about navigated off the entry form and lost this post!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;Wouldn’t that have been funny, my post about how to avoid bad web user experiences lost by a bad web user experiences ;-).&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;Maybe I should change my example to be a blog entry page... &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;Update 2: I tried to upload the VS Solution for this app but I am getting an error... If there is interest in it, I will find another way to post it.. let me know.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;Update 3: I posted the &lt;A href="http://brad_abrams.members.winisp.net/projects/SimpleAjaxForm/SimpleAjaxForm.zip"&gt;zip file for the VS2005 project &lt;/A&gt;so you can see all the details.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Enjoy!&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; FONT-FAMILY: Arial"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=534609" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/02/17/AjaxForRestOfUs.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-17T21:21:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Squeet on Atlas...</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;The &lt;A href="http://www.squeet.com/"&gt;Squeet&lt;/A&gt; folks are &lt;A href="http://squeetblog.blogspot.com/2006/02/microsofts-ajax-library-atlas-rocks.html"&gt;blogging about their usage&lt;/A&gt; of &lt;A href="http://atlas.asp.net/"&gt;Atlas&lt;/A&gt;.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;I can’t wait to see many many more!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=533869" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/02/16/533869.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-16T21:35:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
          <RSSItem>
            <Title>Framework Design Guidelines review and thank you Belgium</Title>
            <Description>&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;David Hayden (a C# MVP) recently posted a &lt;A href="http://codebetter.com/blogs/david.hayden/archive/2006/02/05/137575.aspx"&gt;good review of the FDG&lt;/A&gt;.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;Here is one notable comments:&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" /&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt 0.5in"&gt;&lt;I style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal"&gt;&lt;FONT face=Calibri&gt;Although I was originally worried that it would be more theoretical in nature and mainly apply only to architect types, such is not the case.&amp;nbsp; It is a great combination of 1) best practices concerning fundamental API and class&amp;nbsp;design; 2)&amp;nbsp;great tutorials on .NET framework classes and the when, why, and how to use them; and 3) common design patterns for better manageability and extensibility of your frameworks.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;I style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;FONT face=Calibri&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/I&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;The thanks for this comment has to go to &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = st1 ns = "urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:smarttags" /&gt;&lt;st1:PersonName w:st="on"&gt;Anders Hejlsberg&lt;/st1:PersonName&gt; who very early on in the process of formalizing the guidelines strong encouraged us to keep them very pragmatic and well grounded rather than theoretical.&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P class=MsoNormal style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;&lt;SPAN style="FONT-SIZE: 10pt; COLOR: #8f3b39; FONT-FAMILY: Arial; mso-themecolor: accent2; mso-themeshade: 191"&gt;Oh, and thank you &lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;&lt;st1:country-region w:st="on"&gt;Belgium&lt;/st1:country-region&gt;&lt;/st1:place&gt; – apparently we are the &lt;A href="http://oas2000.proxis.be/gate/jabba.browse_categ.restart2?sc=1000012&amp;amp;si=69128694&amp;amp;p_top=1000011&amp;amp;p_offset=2&amp;amp;p_proc=1."&gt;19&lt;SUP&gt;th&lt;/SUP&gt; Best selling computer book&lt;/A&gt; in the country. &lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;I am sure that &lt;st1:country-region w:st="on"&gt;&lt;st1:place w:st="on"&gt;Belgium&lt;/st1:place&gt;&lt;/st1:country-region&gt; is becoming a center for Framework design excellence!&lt;SPAN style="mso-spacerun: yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;B style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.msdn.com/aggbug.aspx?PostID=529616" width="1" height="1"&gt;</Description>
            <Link>http://blogs.msdn.com/brada/archive/2006/02/10/529616.aspx</Link>
            <pubDate>2006-02-10T08:32:00-05:00</pubDate>
          </RSSItem>
        </Items>
        <LoadedOK>true</LoadedOK>
      </feed>
      <children>
      </children>
    </LRSRSSTreeNode>
  </nodes>
</LRSSTreeNodes>